tharda18: hi
chelsiquixote: morning George
foxubu: Sunday 7:00 AM
FargioFarmani: The champ is back
imaginenation: damn it's georgeee
steinerl: hi guys!
forkdb: Hi
zgamer0123: heyy
foxubu: Is only my stream frozen?
nightknight0000: 3 FPS
tharda18: no
alaouiib: frozen
forkdb: Big fan... what an inspiration you are...
programmerbugx: hi, looking great
f_karamazov: encoding issue
imaginenation: has a beast laptop and internet still so choppy
itoh0: 1fps
TheBloop: hello?
Smyile: Smyile subscribed with Twitch Prime.
worrasenule: Pog, i'm also working some auto prover based on coq atm
imaginenation: slideshow
Merwanedr: What's up Geroge!
mosin_lol: What laptop is he using ?
imaginenation: razor blade
imaginenation: I think
itoh0: now it works
imaginenation: finally
foxubu: ahhh got better
FargioFarmani: "Math waits for nobody." - George Hotz, 2019
forkdb: Please give me tips to be awesome programmer
Merwanedr: I thought it was about METAMASK
andrejnano: hi
vkoskiv: Yo George how do I make my programming streams interesting like yours?
programmerbugx: go live on instagram ! please,
imaginenation: "I'll show you how"
ZemkeCWT: He has sold his Razor Blade. He's on his MacBook 13-inch.
steinerl: @mosin_lol a 13" MacBook Pro I think
imaginenation: oh
spliitzxx: @vkoskiv use a letterlesse keyboard
spliitzxx: less
forkdb: Please give me tips to be awesome programmer
guccibruf: thats a lot of lines
SlightR6: Fuck that
f_karamazov: looks like ass
Cal3b123: send them a link to the refactoring book
vay_man: create your own
ctfnubz420: !uptime
foxubu: George is gonna jump out of the windows
forkdb: Please show me on how to be awesome programmer... like you
shirafx: anyone recomends a good switch for programming? i bought a blue switch one... it's hard and terrible :(
forkdb: It is hhkb
Avraewyn: LUL
programmerbugx: INSTAGRAAAAAM LIVE PLEASE 😎😎😎😎
takkeo: LUL
spliitzxx: lol
neca420: LUL
ragemaster999: @georgehotz have you checked out dlv?
thebastl: @georgehotz build a nice ui for it
shirafx: why did the moderator removed a question?
Merwanedr: I thought it was about METAMASK
takkeo: it's gonna blow your mind NotLikeThis
programmerbugx: HAHAHAH SO STRESS !
dannyboi22457: What IS metamath?
Number___Nine: yyay goerge is back
Number___Nine: !uptime
forkdb: Please show me on how to be awesome programmer... like you
frediiiez: !uptime
OnlyB1ade: So u finally gon do sum productive stuff?
spliitzxx: @forkdb no
Avelansh: and there are free RAMs
programmerbugx: DESCRIBE CHEAP RAM IN MORE DETAILS 🤣🤣🤣🤣
Number___Nine: so is metamath scam?
george_ortolan: There are the LEAN prove theorem too. I don't know if you have already seen it.
npeck0: @frediiiez about 10 mins
Merwanedr: I thought it was about METAMASK
f_karamazov: metamath needs a timeout
Lothsun: How's it going george?
ragemaster999: @georgehotz have you checked out dlv ?
forkdb: @spliitzxx Oknp
LeToutPetitChaton: We need to actually download more rams
Number___Nine: did you really read that whole pdf?
Merwanedr: Do something about METAMASK haha
neca420: real programmers use short illegible names Kappa
dannyboi22457: What is Metamath tho?
Merwanedr: nobody knows
zoki_macola: !uptime
programmerbugx: Where i can find all live sessions by GEORGEHOTZ ? Help
npeck0: @programmerbugx his YT
Merwanedr: youtube: Comma_ai
kektobiologist: can you stream something that i can understand
randoma1: I don’t understand anything of what he is saying.
brisingr1031: pen and paper baby, best proof method
okeeeeeee: allo
machinelearningbot: meth PogChamp
foxubu: Have you been awake all night reading this?
euranymous: Hey George!!
Number___Nine: lol
forkdb: Just chill and enjoy your beautiful day
Number___Nine: we use this stuff at work https://dl.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=2627752
okeeeeeee: maps = win PogChamp
programmerbugx: @npeck0 there are not every stream video of him ! tho
okeeeeeee: thats why you dont understand it
euranymous: can someone clip that hdmaps bit?
Number___Nine: because academics write everything in FORTRAN
FUSiONPlays: LUL
LeadCoder: I stream bro
Ziv0: LUL
euranymous: LUL
Sun__G: LUL
okeeeeeee: LUL
Incurs0: haha
frediiiez: LUL
DriHard: LUL
vkoskiv: Why do math people always refuse to name variables and functions properly? Is it like a law of math?
spliitzxx: lol
f_karamazov: amateur hour
SnakeOneMLG: @georgehotz tell us about meta math
f_karamazov: Ban keyboard guy pls
Number___Nine: vincexviii HHKB2 Pro
shirafx: maybe geo should put the fucking keyboard in the fucking description
serohh: Where are we on prooving true!=false ?
Ralph_124C_41: but these are the important things, who cares about anything else Kappa
Bombapil0t: what brand is your bed geroge ?
Number___Nine: serohh proved that yesterday
geobitz: why dont we talk about the keyboard
Merwanedr: GEORGE PLEASE DO METAMASK not METAMATH
serohh: Oh alright, thanks! @number___nine
okeeeeeee: monkaS
Ziv0: LUL
Incurs0: LUL
frediiiez: f5 guys!
asaalgk: whoa
TheKoreanZombi: Let's get mindful!
MonkaSupreme: headspace bros
asaalgk: i refuse
Bernasv: holy
root_user_198: live meditation
shirafx: ask about timeout = keyboard
751469823: tf
jagger_rsw: whoa, DISTRACTIONS!
root_user_198: somebody donate
鼻史: seems like you earn money yesterday LUL
Jewishrambo: He's back PogChamp
jmc516: The legend has returned
RishabhDeepSingh: Holy tea
frediiiez: george just took a huge bong hits
frediiiez: he is spacing out rn
Bernasv: I feel the power coming out of your head Kappa
st47ik: PogChamp
jagger_rsw: he's hacking his brain rn
ts012839050: Is he turning to god mode?
ashimathilda: timout
st47ik: what hoodie is that?
ashimathilda: timeout
Ralph_124C_41: are we meditating? what is going on?
st47ik: Meditation timeout
jeann2019: mainfull
snapcs1: looks like Augur logo
iTzMeRafa: this isnt even his final form
directrix13: Hotzception
NotFire_: @Ralph_124C_41 please give him time, he is having his moring coffe, aka moring fap
GEEKASHA: is the guy sleeping?
bobsmash: damn I feel relaxed watching this guy
Bernasv: Omg It's envolving Kappa Kappa
prvk3: is he meditating or something
st47ik: achieving enlightenment
GEEKASHA: call 911
st47ik: deep focus PogChamp
鼻史: he is taking off latter
AntiVax_SoccerMom: i can feel my brain growing PogChamp
jagger_rsw: maybe he's got cardiac arrest, and we think he's meditating or sth
Mendacii_: THE SILENT FAP
AntiVax_SoccerMom: this is better than my laser pointer PogChamp
shirafx: quick, ask about keyboards while he's not watching
st47ik: NoNutNovember ez SeemsGood
shirafx: this is the content we need bois
jagger_rsw: is it this AMSR?
Yazik_Yz: I just failed no nut november when I saw George was live
directrix13: He's using mathematical induction to prove properties of his videos
NotKarar: Breathe in Breathe out Kreygasm
prvk3: this is next level content
st47ik: so deep MaN so deep
imsooinhuman: just joined in. what is going on? :D
orex111: what he is doing?
st47ik: he's hacking the simulation
raidersans: PogU
Yazik_Yz: I think he's meditating @imsooinhuman
jagger_rsw: probably watched too much of sam harris
shirafx: trying to figure out why java is good
wrelt: @jagger_rsw kek
Bombapil0t: troll
st47ik: @shirafx LUL
Yazik_Yz: @jagger_rsw not enough psychedelics
raidersans: asmr stream pog
prvk3: LOOOL @shirafx
Bombapil0t: damn troll
tris790: he's channeling his inner chakra
Maybay254: RedCoat
st47ik: Nice PogChamp
ts012839050: Finished?
Bombapil0t: Kreygasm
xyele: what's going on there man
directrix13: Haskell be with you, chat.
st47ik: sip of tea SeemsGood
Bombapil0t: metamath changed him guys
shirafx: when you forgot to lock an object
eduardoadf1: george did dmt again
Bernasv: The tea is essential PogChamp PogChamp
NigerianDrugL0rd: did he fell asleep
funwayz: ResidentSleeper
st47ik: why does he do it live tho
CondomsWontFit: HeyGuys
Jewishrambo: PogChamp 4Head
raidersans: xD
frediiiez: all real hackers do this @st47ik
grimers: favorite eminem album? @georgehotz
root_user_198: omg hes still going i went to make cofee XD
st47ik: damn
Bombapil0t: dont get exploitet by the voice geroge! stand by us
civilist: not sam harris?!
directrix13: Idear
Theguywhobea: i like this :)
shirafx: that was intense
snapcs1: clintSoft
jagger_rsw: nice world salat by this guru
shirafx: sony stand no chance
eduardoadf1: the journey is the answer GUYS @!!!!!!!!!
st47ik: im not 14 and this is deep
AntiVax_SoccerMom: why meditate when you can have a laser pointer helmet 4Head
st47ik: Augur hoodie hacked
TheKoreanZombi: Follow george on insta to get hi-res action shots of him meditating. Or maybe sleeping... Hard to tell.
mystkomir: how is headspace?
Bernasv: Good Morning Kappa Kappa
forkdb: Am now calm and got my composure back
directrix13: You're good enough You're smart enough and gush darn it people like you
MonkaSupreme: so calm Pog
Ralph_124C_41: lol
eduardoadf1: who is this calm guru
shirafx: he found jesus
frediiiez: have we even seen geo this calm?
st47ik: PogChamp
frediiiez: ever*
snapcs1: bob ross programming CoolStoryBob
shirafx: faith++;
atlbullyy: pass the blunt
Bernasv: Geo hotz is that you? Look like a new guy Kappa Kappa Kappa
TheKoreanZombi: Great start
st47ik: @Bernasv he's updated and fresh now
st47ik: BEEP MrDestructoid
raidersans: boop
shirafx: this is the leaked casting of joker
eduardoadf1: monkaS
frediiiez: @shirafx LMAO
jimmyjameshayes100: what is the point of a langauge like MM
directrix13: were the text based adventure games written in prolog?
TheKoreanZombi: I like how the PDF says the file is self explanatory.
anthraxvirus322: Hello Chat what are we doing today
anthraxvirus322: still solving yesterdays problmem ?
vincexviii: Twitch cock Pog
TheKoreanZombi: Why do you concern yourself with ai and metamath when you could just create a meditation app in like 10 minutes and live off the revenue?
anthraxvirus322: @TheKoreanZombi monkaHmm
st47ik: @TheKoreanZombi the point is not to make money i assume 4Head
snapcs1: probably something for verifying proofs @jimmyjameshayes100
myaocat: hi. what's up?
anthraxvirus322: just make money 4Head
TheKoreanZombi: @st47ik Then we are achieving out goal!
st47ik: twitch money is easier 4Head
TheKoreanZombi: *our
st47ik: true
UrWifeMyKids: LUL
AntiVax_SoccerMom: LUL
st47ik: LUL
frediiiez: LUL
eduardoadf1: LUL
Pryetranka: LUL
TheKoreanZombi: Oh no. Did he radicalize you?
meowtit: cmonBruh
anthraxvirus322: Bruh
st47ik: Bruh moment
myaocat: mixing math and templsos...
MrTriharder: George Stream Kreygasm
anthraxvirus322: agree SeemsGood
TheKoreanZombi: Entropy of choosing words yourself is not good though
anthraxvirus322: people have misconception about entropy
frediiiez: yep and easily can be cracked against dictionary attacks
prvk3: what's brain fuck
jimmyjameshayes100: learn lisp next
myaocat: @prvk3 it's fuck your brain
zenkai_oogway: @prvk3 its a language
anthraxvirus322: @prvk3 encoding of a sort
shirafx: i won 2.5k yesterday by bruteforcing a code that should have be found in our snacks, feels good
snapcs1: @prvk3 programming language for genius programmers
anthraxvirus322: stop trolling chat FeelsWeirdman
Mendacii_: META METH INCOMING Kreygasm
prvk3: am i doin it right
TheKoreanZombi: Let's fork metamath and use words. I nominate geohotz as lead dev.
myaocat: have you read about risc-v? It sounds good. I looked it a bit and company utilisize the architecture and made their SoC based on risc-v
worrasenule: quick question why metamath, i thought you were doing coq?
MrTriharder: is talking about old projects still banned? monkaH
Mendacii_: Only true meta math can only be achieved on arch linux
AntiVax_SoccerMom: worrasenule he read some paper on metamath yesterday and seemed like it much more
st47ik: RISC-V is the future Kappa
kkteja: Is there any old stream where george starts learning a new language and builds something?
myaocat: @st47ik money is the future TriHard 7
marvDE1: monkeys are the future
myaocat: yeah! they fix youtube
MrTriharder: George never age. He knows them all already
MrTriharder: learns*
MrTriharder: @georgehotz why are wikipedia articles of math and science trash?
myaocat: can we read about ada lovelace?
myaocat: monkaW
byte_baron: im late to the party here so what's going on exactly guys?
AlexiPexi: What's George's involvement in Comma AI today?
myaocat: @AlexiPexi don't talkabout comma ai please. this is separate thing ..
N0Pro: no comma ai in stream
st47ik: @AlexiPexi George doesn't talk about it on twitch
byte_baron: what is he doing on-screen exactly?
st47ik: @byte_baron metamath
myaocat: wash hands? WutFace
AlexiPexi: All right, thx for letting me know!
MrTriharder: dont talk about , ai monkaS
st47ik: NotLikeThis
myaocat: Gaben
st47ik: $e for essential hypotheses?
forkdb: Cannot understand what he is doing ####
solipsism: what are the use cases for metamath? i just got here
byte_baron: yeah what is the benefit of this exactly?
byte_baron: what's the reason for learning it?
Draco401: @georgehotz What language is that?
redmountain_: coq
byte_baron: it's coq i think
byte_baron: cok
byte_baron: coq
Am4teur: did you used glasses before?
Draco401: Thanks chat
worrasenule: it's metamath
myaocat: what is metameth?
st47ik: this is metamath
worrasenule: another theorem verifier system, similar to coq
st47ik: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Metamath
myaocat: is this the hebrew alphabet?
byte_baron: this is elvish
AntiVax_SoccerMom: http://us.metamath.org/downloads/metamath.pdf he read this yesterday, it convinced him to move from coq to metamath
st47ik: thx mate SeemsGood
myaocat: it's hebrew alphabet
RockyJ0: Hello!
oksan309: Ur profile picture looks awesome SeemsGood
st47ik: MIIIU LUL
prvk3: the whole thing is ugly
byte_baron: was that whiskey
st47ik: nah that's tea
solipsism: i tihnk this is what people imagine programming is when they have no idea about computers
myaocat: how is it related to programming?
st47ik: i mean its math programming 4Head
prvk3: its for his backspace.ai
Santiago_LHC: Hello folks
myaocat: so it's not programming
myaocat: functional programming to prove math proof
byte_baron: it's proving shit
myaocat: yeah but that ain't programming
byte_baron: i know
Santiago_LHC: who cares
byte_baron: it's proving shit
jagger_rsw: RPN stack? Reverse POLISH notation? :) You see w/o my country it'd be possible for George to hack whatever he's hacking
myaocat: @Santiago_LHC you
myaocat: reverse german notation
JanTSV: ouh hey, just came
euranymous: Nationalism at its finest
myaocat: is that logic gates?
vlntnstts: my brain hurt
myaocat: can you debug the code?
anup_kodlekere: !uptime
prvk3: this stream makes me feal like an idiot everytime i tune in, i barely understand anything he does ever
crazywulf770: can someone explain for a laic like me what this is and what is it useful for?
anup_kodlekere: you dont watch this stream, this is for background purposes only
zgamer0123: @prvk3 ur not the only one xd
snapcs1: its for verifying mathematical proofs
zgamer0123: yes but george is the only one understanding all this shirt
anup_kodlekere: it's just a sneak peek into ho he thinks and solves problems. it's not really meant for us.
anup_kodlekere: how*
jagger_rsw: I was thinking that everyone is using ML to solve all known problems these days. Why not George train some model to write this proof for him?
myaocat: @crazywulf770 i assure you that if you TriHard 7 eventually you wwill get it
snapcs1: you guys obviously dont have a compsci degree lol
anup_kodlekere: thats bs. ML for everything is overkill
jagger_rsw: I hae comp-SCSI degree
crazywulf770: myaocat :-D
snapcs1: then you would know ML doesnt really make sense for this problem
myaocat: really
byte_baron: just ML it!!!
prvk3: @jagger_rsw he talked about that yesterday but i dont remember what he exactly said, i think he said he'd be really mad if that was the actual solution
TheTrueJonsel: What's he doing?
zenkai_oogway: just use ML bro 4Head
euranymous: is this stream for playing in the background just to distract me from my loneliness?
oksan309: Programming asmr LUL
worrasenule: people are ML-ing it, it's not very easy
jagger_rsw: just use ML
myaocat: @crazywulf770 i tried so hard and got so far but in the end it doesn't even matter
okeeeeeee: Clap
euranymous: LUL
anup_kodlekere: btw is he using browns?
Ziv0: LUL
anup_kodlekere: or blues?
Cal3b123: Did we prove MU can't be derived from MI?
CondomsWontFit: So cumbersome
syska: i hate c++ just putting it out there :)
myaocat: @syska really not matter
crazywulf770: myaocat yeah... looks very very very times 10 time consuming
myaocat: @syska c++ hate you back
anup_kodlekere: c++ sad...
myaocat: @crazywulf770 yeah that's how it works.
syska: :(
myaocat: in CTF, everything
prafaeltsantos: c++, is nice.....
myaocat: there is no free meal in life
myaocat: no free fish
listrk: metameth
euranymous: What keyboard do you use? @georgehotz
anup_kodlekere: @listrk lol
frediiiez: someone got timed out
solipsism: monkaS he asked
frediiiez: LUL
redIet_: HeyGuys
frediiiez: @euranymous read the description below the stream
LegalFever: what the fuck is going on
euranymous: LUL
Lefer_: He used to use one of the Leopolds without numpad, right now HHKB I think
Santiago_LHC: I see that we are already onto keyboard talk
syska: 300$ keyboard MonkaS
prafaeltsantos: @euranymous it´s a HHKB2, and we dont make that question bro, dont ask specs.....he gets mad
oksan309: @Legal just watch and enjoy LUL
Lefer_: The real question is why is he using vi instead of vim
solitaryyy: back to vim Kappa
rennerp: just for pleasure i guess
Infinitelym: are they not the same?
anup_kodlekere: how do you debug if you're writing everything in vi or vim
oksan309: @Lefer he likes it classic LUL
Lefer_: LUL
ppnn123w: he doing this on desktop or laptop
ghostfrommarz: the real real question is, wut is this
Santiago_LHC: Laptop
Santiago_LHC: Here is his setup: https://www.instagram.com/p/Bx0DMrUAxE-/
sirdicholas: sirdicholas subscribed with Twitch Prime.
solipsism: do u rly think a 0 day is part of his threat model @myaocat
euranymous: Someone needs to make a meme about his keyboard
haircutjimmy: Hi George - good to see you streaming again.
ppnn123w: @Santiago_LHC ty
anup_kodlekere: cant understand shit
Ziv0: wat LUL
Lefer_: LUL
god_damn: get that guy outta here
Santiago_LHC: The hackers are always after the metamath
Malinax: millionaire metamath right here
anup_kodlekere: what is "the cloud"?
pizzamcprice: hi G
Bombapil0t: TriHard
euranymous: Can we do a ask GEOHOT stream?
VitalyzedTv: LUL
zenkai_oogway: LUL
Lazylion2: imagine asking about a keyboard
Mendacii_: VIM sucks
OsurdumGaliba: LUL
sulozor: nvim > vim Pog
theduckthough: the audacity
zenkai_oogway: I am just here for the occasional rants
syska: ^ban this guy!
zenkai_oogway: monkaS
prafaeltsantos: oioioioi VIM is the GOAT
yodiggity4739: this guy bricked my first iphone Kappa
euranymous: ask geohot but no keyboard and machine stuff just some genuine questions!!
Santiago_LHC: If you are a regular, you'd know that the keyboard question gets asked every 5 seconds.
frediiiez: my programming editor is Microsoft Word
theduckthough: so how do they verify that their prover works
yodiggity4739: is he still working on self driving cars
oksan309: Easy easy smart boy not all are as smart as u BabyRage
Cal3b123: why would they commit compressed proofs
xenoshiva: @euranymous no but if he gets the same keyboard as geo he can be as great as him!!
solipsism: does whitespace matter in metamath or is it just for your own preferences
pizzamcprice: what is he building?
Santiago_LHC: @yodiggity4739 He is, but that's another bannable topic here
gluecks: what keyboard (piano) do u have? glueck4Chopin
yodiggity4739: monkaS
syska: @xenoshiva very true
sulozor: what do you do in your day-to-day life ? still on the self driving company? @georgehotz
theduckthough: what is you plan for how the language should look like?
Lefer_: cmonBruh
theduckthough: or just following the book?
prvk3: what's the .g file type?
solipsism: can u guys really not think of questions related to what he is actively showing us?
anup_kodlekere: grammar
euranymous: @xenoshiva LUL
yodiggity4739: what is he going to apply this math to or is it just for fun
Lefer_: as if any of us had an idea what is he doing LUL
prvk3: holy shit lark is so cool wtf
pizzamcprice: what is he doing? just typing random code?
Kimx_: Im enjoying him being productive while I am just lazy
Atlas03: the keyboard sounds so Kreygasm
solipsism: yes he is typing random characters and hoping nobody in stream notices @pizzamcprice
yodiggity4739: he is unlocking the secret math of the universe
euranymous: tmux and vim ; The only description of a one badass programmer
robotboy987: I think geohotz could be asmr influencer with his keyboard sounds
theduckthough: this is actually pretty cool so you create axioms and notation from first order logic (is it?) and then proof the truth of derived statements (theorems). do you use the ZFC or some other commonly used set of axioms for that then?
MrTriharder: Fun fact: all math in universe boils down to 1 TheIlluminati TheIlluminati
ppnn123w: outlook vs gmail ?
Atlas03: what is 1 then bubuHmm
pizzamcprice: @solipsism LUL but seriously what is he building?
MrTriharder: There’s asmr influencers now? DansGame
robotboy987: outlook is sucks
yodiggity4739: i think hes doing math puzzles
prafaeltsantos: what is a "1" fore aliens?=
Santiago_LHC: check the title
Cal3b123: 1 is the successor of 0
MrTriharder: @prafaeltsantos Zeta
euranymous: I dont understand shit but I like the energy he is putting into the work
solipsism: @pizzamcprice he's doing test exercises to see how he feels about metamath i think
theduckthough: in modern math we define one to be a set that contains one element so 1:=}
yodiggity4739: is there a command that lists all the bannable topics
Kimx_: use common sense
prafaeltsantos: @MrTriharder but that is a complex number
Santiago_LHC: Mentioning the list is a bannable topic
GryphoonAOE: what are you trying to program @georgehotz
yodiggity4739: monkaS
robotboy987: if I put so much work on Sunday I might graduate PhD in 4 weeks 😂
euranymous: LUL
worrasenule: looks like he's trying to build a metamath parser
pizzamcprice: @solipsism ah i see, danke.
kingb9b: metameth
MrTriharder: @prafaeltsantos Aliens have figured out working with complex numbers
theduckthough: "metameth" LUL
W1lkins: always types meth
ᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞ: ez B)
crazywulf770: a metamath WHAT?
W1lkins: suspect
GryphoonAOE: what is a metamath?
syska: meth-a-math :)
Santiago_LHC: Google is your friend
yodiggity4739: ah yes a metamath verifier 🍷 indeed
vmarkushin: meta-meth?
anup_kodlekere: metameta
MrTriharder: Chat don’t type drug references monkaS u might suffer the wrath of ban
xevilcorp: oh, he came back
prafaeltsantos: @MrTriharder maybe complex number for "them" is like "1 2 3 4 5" for us
Santiago_LHC: When he goes to the bathroom that's my favorite part of the stream, because I understand what is happening.
yodiggity4739: that looks like a pretty nice fridge
euranymous: What are bannable topics?
theduckthough: @prafaeltsantos that makes no sense
MrTriharder: @prafaeltsantos And our 1234 is their complex numbers
robotboy987: this guys just pees, programs and repeat..... jezzzz
Santiago_LHC: Bannable topics: Keyboard, setup questions, comma ai
zgamer0123: Metamath seems to be proof of mathematics
anup_kodlekere: @euranymous self driving cars, his setup
yodiggity4739: @georgehotz what kind of fridge is that
euranymous: and chews some eyes
euranymous: @anup_kodlekere Thanks man
prafaeltsantos: @MrTriharder lets make a series about this for History channel and get rich
zgamer0123: @yodiggity4739 do u wanna be banned? XDD
Kimx_: This chat is pretty bad, but overall the quality is still better than 99% of all other twitch chats that just spams emotes all day
theduckthough: metamath seems to be a language to formulate mathematical proofs for the computer to understand and verify
yodiggity4739: i asked about his fridge setup monkaS
MrTriharder: @prafaeltsantos Or we’ve only been thinking numbers on 2 axis. One is the real numbers. One is complex numbers. What about a 3 rd axis ? Kappa
iTeQo_: Damn wrong stream. I was looking für crystal meth
Kimx_: @MrTriharder thats called quaternion
anup_kodlekere: @theduckthough but how does it wrk though? you give it a theorem and it gets the proof?
prafaeltsantos: @theduckthough we are talking about "things" that fly on frisbee
MrTriharder: WutFace people actually know this ?
Kimx_: Yes
swills6: @mrtriharder third is imaginary
MrTriharder: What about 4th axis Kappa
n3bojsa: lol
Kimx_: That would be your mom
theduckthough: @anup_kodlekere we derive the truth of a theorem with axioms (statements that are just said to be true) so it checks if the theorem is not in violation of the axioms
MrTriharder: No aliens have figured out axis’s up to 5.
yodiggity4739: so u just need a bunch of if statements
yodiggity4739: 4Head
prafaeltsantos: @MrTriharder and if we and the 4rd axis and we can have a time correlation
euranymous: HELLOOOOOO
anup_kodlekere: @theduckthough niiice, well if I was in his place I'd probably just brute force for all inputs. I'm not sure that'd work though, not a mathematician
zoki_macola: hes pooping
gabrielpolastrini: i need laptops recommendations
AdmiraIGoldenRetriever: He's back, stream is froze, press F5 Kappa
MrTriharder: Aliens have a 5 dimension Pythagoras theorem :)
anup_kodlekere: lol
euranymous: There's actually a third dimensional pythagorean theorem
theduckthough: @anup_kodlekere no you have to construct the proof with logical connections of statements and theorems and what not that doesnt really make sense to bruteforce
euranymous: Its called the super pythogorous relation or something like that
MrTriharder: DansGame
Number___Nine: what
yodiggity4739: this is hard to understand maybe i should just stick with watching pokimane
prafaeltsantos: if I ask @georgehotz about is process of getting verified on Instagram i will get a ban? UWot TheIlluminati TearGlove
MrTriharder: How do u people such things DansGame
anup_kodlekere: @theduckthough this only works for discrete mathematics right? like predicate calculus, logic and shit?
euranymous: JaVasCript:alert(document.cookie)//
Akash_44: 5Heads in chat
Number___Nine: I though geohot ragequit metamath
euranymous: LUL
solipsism: pokiW
prafaeltsantos: Pythagoras has a alien from Delta 69
aPosterior: @theduckthough that insistance itself is an axiom, not to mention its details
robotboy987: @georgehotz is living eat shit program repeat... damn
Number___Nine: living the dream
anup_kodlekere: can I ask interesting projects to implement in python? or will I be banned?
MrTriharder: What if the Big Bang was an aliens firecracker for New Year’s Eve? 5Head
Kimx_: youll be banned if you keep asking if youre gonna get banned
iTeQo_: Pythagoras stole from reddit. Check twitter
euranymous: LUL
robotboy987: @anup_kodlekere make a twitch bot
luckiehem: hey man what chair u got
Bombapil0t: TriHard
yodiggity4739: can we ask who his favorite female streamer is
theduckthough: @anup_kodlekere depends what kind of logic some statements cannot be made with first order logic (which i am guessing this is) but most of mathemtics can be done with this logic for sure (if you're interested in this from the ground up reasoning the the bourbaki group might be for you)
grizvok: holy shit my wish is granted
grizvok: george is streaming again
n3bojsa: @georgehotz whats the hoodie ur wearing?
grimers: georgehotz whats your favorite eminem album
Number___Nine: it looks like a gnu make
grizvok: grizvok is gifting 5 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 5 in the channel!
grizvok: grizvok gifted a Tier 1 sub to jagger_rsw!
grizvok: grizvok gifted a Tier 1 sub to W1lkins!
grizvok: grizvok gifted a Tier 1 sub to twiggy_io!
grizvok: grizvok gifted a Tier 1 sub to Orestes13!
grizvok: grizvok gifted a Tier 1 sub to knilecrack!
MrTriharder: Subaru release monkaS
yodiggity4739: i got one Pog
W1lkins: Pog
Number___Nine: husky
alreye: lol
MrTriharder: I dodged it PogChamp
grimers: PrimeMe
AdmiraIGoldenRetriever: PogChamp DODGED
yodiggity4739: these hackers are at least 70 years old
Jannnik: dodged Pog
Bombapil0t: @grizvok u can ask him about his keyboard at least 5 times now gz!
MrTriharder: @admiraigoldenretriever Do u come on bulldogs stream? Billy336
Akash_44: pog
salpu_: ryrySkime ryrySkime ryrySkime
zenkai_oogway: PogChamp
ᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞ: KappaCool
grimers: Pog
alchemist_ubi: hahahahahaa
syska: lOl
euranymous: George I really wanna thank you for inspiring me.
worrasenule: monkaH
grizvok: THE POWER.
Bombapil0t: :D
yodiggity4739: monkaS
Number___Nine: ban the planet
ᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞ: MingLee
iTzMeRafa: xDD
parse: ban me :)
alchemist_ubi: Twitch chat OMEGALUL
luckiehem: lulz
Akash_44: monkaS
alchemist_ubi: monkaS
zenkai_oogway: MonkaSupreme
tris790: gratz
zenkai_oogway: monkaS
alxhotel: grizvok dont ban me plis
mathieu_696: PogChamp
salpu_: LUL
Zanfr1980: money power!
alreye: He bought his way in LUL
yodiggity4739: money PogU
alchemist_ubi: actually true KEKW
euranymous: @grizvok Congratzz
prafaeltsantos: can a mod ban himself?
mathieu_696: true lmao
guy_ross: guy_ross subscribed at Tier 1.
Number___Nine: ban geohot
euranymous: LUL
alxhotel: a mod for the mods ?
MrTriharder: monkaS
nesaniica: grizvok, give me a 5 minute timeout FeelsGoodMan
alchemist_ubi: imagine using LUL in 2019 KEKW
euranymous: Every thing is in your github repo right @georgehotz
theduckthough: @georgehotz what does statement mean in this context?
grizvok: I code in php for my work fml
grimers: rip
randoma1: Rip
alxhotel: php will survive python mark my words
tris790: feelsphpman
Bombapil0t: you can afford subs so that's fine i guess
euranymous: RIP
grizvok: why they decided not to go for a python web framework i will never know
W1lkins: it will at least survive 2.7 alxhotel Kappa
syska: g++ compiler is so nice the error messages are very understandable PepeHands
yodiggity4739: i code in wingdings and then convert it to english
MrTriharder: Php more like RIP KEKW
euranymous: george might remove you as a mod @grizvok
W1lkins: grizvok you're at least on php7 right?
nesaniica: php mods DansGame
alxhotel: yep W1lkins
notmap: wat u doing?
grimers: so this means this channel fully endorses php?
grizvok: @W1lkins yep. I've only used php for 4 months since i've been at this new company. Honestly this web framework symfony is pretty nice.
alchemist_ubi: php best language ever Kapp
luckiehem: php is great
grizvok: But I'd rather be working in flask
duzy: Whats the best 1st lang to learn
MrTriharder: It isn’t a language when everything is global is it?
theduckthough: english
dr_koili: Laravel is amazing. Shame its so tainted with the baggage of old php
notmap: php is garbo
alxhotel: @duzy brainfuck
duzy: nice
Bombapil0t: asmr Kreygasm
grizvok: php doesn't really have that global problem anymore so far as I've seen
luckiehem: @dr_koili i agree
euranymous: George are you into esoteric languages?
alxhotel: php 7 is much better than previous versions
twitch7443: morning people
Cetewyn: topre keyboard Kreygasm
randoma1: What is he coding?
Attlantiz_: whats up george
syska: best language is lisp
theduckthough: so does metamath allow you to abstract away smaller theorems?
yodiggity4739: he is coding a simulation of the universe
W1lkins: which language is best for building a parser such as thing @georgehotz
robotboy987: if only topre was cheap FailFish
Cetewyn: cheap keyboards LUL
Attlantiz_: he does
alchemist_ubi: what is he coding btw?
MrTriharder: Ban monkaS
Number___Nine: alchemist_ubi metamath parser in pyton using lark
MrTriharder: Never talk about drugs here monkaS
xrealyy: he's coding metamath kind of thing
alchemist_ubi: what the heck is metamath perser?
Attlantiz_: methmat
Attlantiz_: george have you heard about flutter
alchemist_ubi: is that eatable? I see a lot of metamath people in LA
EderDG: have you ever tried coding for 3D animation?
grizvok: he messed with unity i think for a bit on stream a while ago
YouPowerRush: ayy lamo
st47ik: Unity was for AR stuff
annasgrasshopper: you followed me on linkdin haha
Attlantiz_: flutter is cool for mobile apps
alchemist_ubi: monkaS
annasgrasshopper: followed me back*
nesaniica: no drugs, no keyboards and no iphones in here
Bombapil0t: just tea and metamath Kreygasm
Attlantiz_: just android
W1lkins: no iphones? DansGame
alchemist_ubi: higher what? I am having English trouble
Attlantiz_: Kappa
syska: communist
nesaniica: also no self driving cars, we dont talk about that
theduckthough: 1000 iq audience
Attlantiz_: I wish I knew more about that stuff
Attlantiz_: coq and stuff
alchemist_ubi: hahahahahah
robotboy987: let's talk about simulation
Tusk_TV: get banned nerds Kappa
grimers: what if im not smart monkaS
bool3max: that's why chat rooms are coming
MrTriharder: Like me? :)
MonkaSupreme: hello i know nothing about that stuff, but im subbed TehePelo
ickystickybandit: let's talk about Jesus
raulciuntastefan: can i hear an amen ?
0x7f_: im 12 what is this?
YouPowerRush: haha
4play_: Did someone mention drugs?
n3bojsa: @georgehotz where is that goodie from?
Attlantiz_: what are you doing in this stream?
n3bojsa: I see you wear it quite often
alchemist_ubi: well dude, how the person knows if he is smart or not if the person doesnt speak in front of smart people?
Attlantiz_: what does the python script do?
P4NiiC_LIVE: everytime I come here I feel dumb LUL
alaouiib: are u smart 🤠👨💻
Hellsing14: free speech for the dumb
whichtom: How long has geo been live for today
AdmiraIGoldenRetriever: my mum said i am smart :)
MorbidlyBrobese: this is my favorite dictatorship
st47ik: LUL
alchemist_ubi: I could be the smartest person in the room inside my head LUL
grizvok: @alchemist_ubi their achievements?
Attlantiz_: what does the python script do? isnt that metamath?
n3bojsa: fkin nerd
alchemist_ubi: @grizvok that is the most basic answer you could ever give, think deeper, that is too basic
grimers: this chat is in big brain mode now
nesaniica: LUL
MonkaSupreme: LUL
raulciuntastefan: lol
st47ik: rekt LUL
prafaeltsantos: LUL LUL
MrTriharder: All the chat peeps show us your 5Head
Wansie: LUL
raulciuntastefan: cannabis is life
YouPowerRush: haaaa
MrTriharder: LUL
Attlantiz_: can anyone please explain what the python script does
tris790: LUL
Bombapil0t: no drugs @Cetewyn
alphagainzzz: LUL
solipsism: i wonder if slow mode would help
YouPowerRush: <message banned>
prafaeltsantos: a fcking love geo, he always makes my day
grizvok: @alchemist_ubi sorry that literally means nothing to me
markovrandomfield: What about Lean? :tf:
Attlantiz_: is it a parser for metamath?
grimers: cmonBruh
beninr1: Hi from Kosovo GEORGE
ProfElements1: @attlantiz_ He making a python script to verify the meta math things he is doing.
mexeroserisback: Yeah Lean seems nice
Attlantiz_: oh, but doesnt metamath do that?
Attlantiz_: wait is metamath like coq?
st47ik: we need a bot that detects keywords and bans ppl for talking about the forbidden stuff Kappa
Attlantiz_: ^
oksan309: celluOoof
InertPackage: Are you typing in QWERTY?
grimers: doesnt nightbot do that? @st47ik
InertPackage: Hi brow people only type in Dvorak
theduckthough: keyboard man bad
InertPackage: Kappa
st47ik: stop talking about keyboards NotLikeThis MaN
MonkaSupreme: @theduckthough bye
euranymous: You better subscribe
MrTriharder: Every time George looks at this monitor, someone gets a ban monkaS
theduckthough: ahsh
Bombapil0t: and follow on instagram asap @InertPackage
MonkaSupreme: @theduckthough sub or die riPepperonis
InertPackage: I'm too high brow. I don't use instagram, FB, or Twitter.
st47ik: the bio literally says it all btw
euranymous: George seriously deserves a verification badge in instagram
InertPackage: I occasionally reddit. That's about it.
alchemist_ubi: @st47ik LUL I didnt see it monkaS
grimers: damn u must be real smart
InertPackage: Like front page /r/iamverysmart
UMPS: but you're on twitch so you're back at 0
alchemist_ubi: just get them 4Head
forkdb: Use PyCharm instead
alchemist_ubi: yeah use PyCharm monkaS
MrTriharder: monkaS don’t talk about editors
alchemist_ubi: I am not smart monkaS
UMPS: is he running tmux?
TheRealFreki: why don't you add keyboard cam :)
solipsism: yes @UMPS
UMPS: i like his setup, it looks nice and clean
Number___Nine: UMPS tmux and vim splits
MrTriharder: For whatever reasons I can get fast enough in vim
MrTriharder: Cant *
zoki_macola: https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1159655968369565696?lang=en
alchemist_ubi: @MrTriharder dont worry, I will just take you 3 years to get tehre
prafaeltsantos: the real question is, we will have breaded chicken agen?
Keyeh: can we talk abou treelon musk george?
Number___Nine: Microsoft Word
lazystoic: I'm too stupid to understand whats going on here, please explain someone
Number___Nine: for ASCII editing
alchemist_ubi: I think Twitch chat is too smart for him monkaS Imagine taking it seriously LUL
alchemist_ubi: I should Jebaited but I will get ban thou monkaS
MrTriharder: At least we dumb people get to be on YouTube FeelsGoodMan Clap
solipsism: what is the difference between Jebaited and being actually stupid though @alchemist_ubi
alchemist_ubi: @solipsism your comment
UMPS: monkaS
Keyeh: we can't talk about comma.ai in here
ᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞ: monkaS
alchemist_ubi: @MrTriharder will this be publish to YouTube monkaS
MrTriharder: @alchemist_ubi I think
grimers: monkaS
MrTriharder: monkaS
FackingNeckbeards: what is he programming in?
alchemist_ubi: @FackingNeckbeards Python
FackingNeckbeards: what IDE?
Wnb_Gosu: george, do you play some games ?
MrTriharder: Very
MrTriharder: Vim
UMPS: i'm watching someone else program so i feel less bad about wasting time while not programming
solipsism: stop asking setup questions guys this is not that hard
solipsism: literally 30 seconds and another setup question
VitalyzedTv: what text editor is that? ( im a noob )
solipsism: 0 seconds
Wnb_Gosu: google it
grimers: LUL
OnlyB1ade: wait... when did u go live again?
AntiVax_SoccerMom: like an hour ago
MrTriharder: @solipsism What wire is he using? :)
grizvok: wait changing my editor doesn't make me a better programmer?
prafaeltsantos: !uptime
alchemist_ubi: Hello Google: what editor does george use?
grimers: it makes you a better programmer if you use vim
yaus_baus: !uptime
UMPS: >:|
alchemist_ubi: @grimers it makes you a better typer, maybe LUL
PepeHypers: @grimers no
maskerlive: !project
345kiwi: what's going on right now lol
vmarkushin: @PepeHypers of course yes. Didn't you know that?
yaus_baus: how long has he been streaming
UMPS: how old is everyone
UMPS: im 12
Attlantiz_: I'm 5
MrTriharder: monkaS
maskerlive: im 60
alchemist_ubi: @scorpiocyborg Jebaited
alchemist_ubi: monkaS
hazrid93: wow basic programming? just the basic right sounds easy Pepega
Attlantiz_: Kappa dude got banned
FackingNeckbeards: nice kitchen tho
worrasenule: Krappa
krakendmp: krakendmp subscribed with Twitch Prime.
alchemist_ubi: I feel bad for him now heheheheh
VitalyzedTv: dont ban me pl0x monkaS
Keyeh: this is his bedroom though @FackingNeckbeards
ᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞᆞ: RarePepe
Keyeh: LUL
yaus_baus: hey george, quit my job after yesterdays vod, will be homeless soon. what do next? luv stream btw
FackingNeckbeards: i didnt even notice the bed LuL
Bombapil0t: its called cloud @Keyeh
Wnb_Gosu: what does he even trying
Wnb_Gosu: cant figure out
cybermajestic: hello george
aureal1: imagine mentioning the word keyboard Kappa
Sniky83: Hi Georges, are you still in hacking area ?
c4rb4rus: please find an exploit in the simulation, George
alchemist_ubi: yes yes monkaHmm
InertPackage: Terribly low brow people that come a channel playing in "Basic Programming" How can these idiots not realize High Brow only in Basic Programming. If you want your copy pasta go to Science and Technology plebs
FackingNeckbeards: what?
grimers: georgehotz whats your favorite eminem album
grizvok: yes, yes they did
dorkmo: yessss
yaus_baus: i wish i was intelligent enough to say highbrow stuff
alchemist_ubi: alchemist_ubi subscribed at Tier 1.
alchemist_ubi: chat I am big brain and you are not LUL
dorkmo: every once in a while some random dude thats an expert shows up tho
alchemist_ubi: get rekt
alchemist_ubi: monkaS shit shit
alchemist_ubi: @dorkmo like me Kappa
Wnb_Gosu: test
Number___Nine: C++20 though
AntiVax_SoccerMom: i mean its from like the 90s right?
forkdb: Ok np
VitalyzedTv: yay <3
dorkmo: TheIlluminati TheIlluminati
MrBankster: howdy
grimers: what inspired you to start this project george
zoki_macola: test test 123
dorkmo: MercyWing1 TheIlluminati TheIlluminati MercyWing2
AntiVax_SoccerMom: why not DansGame
eeqeq: hi
Number___Nine: video is gone, oh no
Rojaster: some coke I need to get it through
Bombapil0t: freeplebs yay
worrasenule: so xx means a node in ast monkaHmm
Number___Nine: and it's back
yaus_baus: jesus fuck the miu2.mm looks like heiroglyphics
Number___Nine: yeah, even APL looks readable compared to that
euranymous: my brain needs some steroids to understand these
xHardcorexism: supp
grizvok: @euranymous just use near infrared light bro
yaus_baus: is the dollar letter like variable assignments in bash?
euranymous: @georgehotz Can you zoom a little bit
euranymous: @grizvok Looking forward to it
script_sh: there is a box on the floor
4e696b6c6173: hi
CaptainAshtar: apple ofcourse...
euranymous: LUL
preporyan: LUL
CaptainAshtar: i thought it would be chips or ... cheetos but an apple
MonkaSupreme: how can one quit working for the man? @georgehotz
euranymous: eating apple instead of buying iphones
MonkaSupreme: damn thats deep
scorpiocyborg: @euranymous u should become a rapper
endeavor_42: hey what's up
CasparBaIT: oi
preporyan: OK, what is he doing? I'm not familiar with all this at all
brisingr1031: @georgehotz how much time a day do you spend coding/reading about cs stuff?
euranymous: @scorpiocyborg Will drop something on sound cloud someday
CaptainAshtar: whats behind intelligence i really don't understand how a person can develop such brain power to do all this can someone explain
AntiVax_SoccerMom: CaptainAshtar try shining infrared lights at your brain
grizvok: Yes
yaus_baus: george been doing this for years man
yaus_baus: @CaptainAshtar
CaptainAshtar: i said intelligence not monkey ticks
ridolf88: why people asking about his keyboard is it like a meme or something?
mitchell_344: Brains like a muscle, you work hard and it will grow
CaptainAshtar: infrared lights ... couldn't you think of something else ... pills, food, toilet water
Sublimus7: dumb questions get dumb answers
ProfessorMagikarp0: how was the rest of the book without chat LUL
mitchell_344: hes using the Happy Hacking Keyboard Pro 2
euranymous: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=21042018
euranymous: LUL
yaus_baus: honestly if i wanted to actually follow his work rn i would need to spend a week writing a proof in metamath
scorpiocyborg: @mitchell_344 watch out you might get banned for saying the M-word
Sublimus7: @euranymous holy shit what am I reading
scorpiocyborg: K-word*
euranymous: Infrared lights
CaptainAshtar: wtf is that related to your brain i don't undestand
AntiVax_SoccerMom: k gonna read a 240 page book so i can watch the stream SeemsGood
ProfessorMagikarp0: chat got an F on homework PepeHands
yaus_baus: was busy doing EDA :(
MonkaSupreme: have you read the book?
AntiVax_SoccerMom: i read the preface PogChamp
euranymous: @AntiVax_SoccerMom Or just get your child a polio shot?
Keyeh: in life sometimes there is question marks :)
raulciuntastefan: what book ? metamath from metamath.org ?
Sublimus7: was busy pursuing my dreams of being a rapper
AntiVax_SoccerMom: euranymous that causes autism honey
yaus_baus: book: http://us.metamath.org/downloads/metamath.pdf
TheKoreanZombi: This chat is 30% "What IDE is this", 20% banned topics 40% "Durr this is hard.", and 10% useful talk.
yaus_baus: thats what hes referencing
euranymous: @AntiVax_SoccerMom You're funny
raulciuntastefan: thanks
Santiago_LHC: @TheKoreanZombi that's mankind for you
endeavor_42: !time
mufeedvh: hey George, can i work with you?
grimers: 10% is really generous
Sublimus7: !uptime
annasgrasshopper: you should try program with Kerbal Space program and ebat SpaceX at their game
CaptainAshtar: that's because the stramer is doing monolog all the time
TheKoreanZombi: @grimers True. and useful is overstating it as well.
yaus_baus: @Sublimus7 based on his first commit in the metamath hes been streaming for over an hour
Santiago_LHC: Two hours
yaus_baus: @Santiago_LHC thanks
euranymous: @georgehotz Do you have a plan of writing a book about something in future?
Number___Nine: a book about metamath
euranymous: or about not working for the man
yaus_baus: if george says its weird.... lol
endeavor_42: !uptime
thekillerens0: !keyboard
thekillerens0: !timeout
Sublimus7: classis arc of computer programming right there
VitalyzedTv: !commands
Sublimus7: classic*
davidbarreroo: lil recap ??
death_gadget: Isn't the end tag $) not )$
swagettiyolonaise69: "basic programming"
keetio: sup georgio
Sublimus7: @death_gadget ... nice
DasMastah: The end of the regex is wrong
DasMastah: It should be $) not )$
euranymous: the basic programming should be changed to 'Brainfuck'
CaptainAshtar: its correct
essSau: is that vi or vim
essSau: with emacs
euranymous: vim is improved vi
yaus_baus: vim with tmux
Rezii27: Hello
Rezii27: i really need to learn vim
CaptainAshtar: learn it then
euranymous: add powerline to the mix and you have pimp of all terminals
VitalyzedTv: how long does it take to learn vim?
Bo0sted05: what are you doing exactly?
grimers: why do you "need to" learn vim ?
yaus_baus: @VitalyzedTv not long man, just use it as your text editor and youll get faster with time
euranymous: learning vim isnt that hard
DR4GOM1R: what is he making}
DR4GOM1R: ?
AntiVax_SoccerMom: Bo0sted05 i think hes trying to prove the MU puzzle in metamath
euranymous: just print out a reference and keep it near by and you'll remember everything after some time using it
yaus_baus: or just google the commands/motions for vim as if it was syntax for any other language
VitalyzedTv: ok thx for the advice
yaus_baus: theres a vim plugin for metamath george
Number___Nine: http://emetamath.tirix.org/
yaus_baus: https://github.com/david-a-wheeler/vim-metamath
yaus_baus: idk if useful
grizvok: it might be
yaus_baus: oh lmao its by david a wheeler
alxhotel: a
breadhamandcheese: ello
yaus_baus: yeah ill admit i google and paste before reading
alxhotel: so the aim is to do a verifier to verify metamath programs ?
yaus_baus: lmao
0xh4sh: Oh damn, I actually made it to a Geohot stream lissie1Awww
unrandomknown: no difference LUL
yaus_baus: i made no promises
worrasenule: A |- B means B can be derived given A.|- A means A is theorem, or simply, A can be derived, or A is an axiom.
worrasenule: there's a wiki page for ti
ravicat: chat can you tell me what is he trying to solve/write?
worrasenule: *it
worrasenule: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turnstile_(symbol)
filedescriptor: @ravicat no one knows
ravicat: @filedescriptor is this how it usually is or sth?
CaptainAshtar: as i was going to ask what is the purpose of the stream
AntiVax_SoccerMom: whoahh
breadhamandcheese: PogChamp
CaptainAshtar: it's metamath you hear guys
ProfessorMagikarp0: math-ception
ravicat: LUL
YouPowerRush: metamath confirmt ?
Mendacii_: I don’t know what it means, but sounds provocative LUL
ProfessorMagikarp0: ^ this guy gets it
ProfessorMagikarp0: it gets the people going
CaptainAshtar: you don't need to know the metamath just watch the apple
yaus_baus: friendship with coq is over, now metamath is best friend
mltsd: just eat apple guys
yaus_baus: tldr of stream
mitchell_344: keep up the good work George!
AntiVax_SoccerMom: boomer code
ProfessorMagikarp0: @yaus_baus these programmers aint loyal Kappa
CaptainAshtar: he doesn't accept cheers if you don't know metamath
Number___Nine: or FORTH
CaptainAshtar: and you are not eating an apple
marluo5: yeah im considering that source file
marluo5: i totally get it
ProfessorMagikarp0: good apple marketing needs a sponsor
micos7: I didnt know you are an Apple guy
oksan309: Man why don't u take a break and walk around a little bit
ProfessorMagikarp0: apple asmr
notbigd: has he gotten to for loops yet?
yaus_baus: more tendies
mltsd: !uptime
mitchell_344: sauce and fries
CaptainAshtar: that's how geniuses are eating an apple equal from all sides with double check on the angles
zigzati: @professormagikarp0 cosmic crisp apple has a $10 mil marketing budget
mitchell_344: i prefer pears usually more
yaus_baus: geroge applies mouth algorithm to apple
micos7: Bruh do you even tea?
mltsd: so what will the finished program be able to do?
CaptainAshtar: to calculate metamath
micos7: Will be able to color the background of a div Kappa
inciMage: gfg is amazing but sometimes they fk my brain up at algorithms section
DR4GOM1R: !keyboard
thyssen: !keyboard
inciMage: hhkb2
micos7: !mouse
yaus_baus: no keeb talk bois
mltsd: look at text below stream oh now
mltsd: no
filedescriptor: @DR4GOM1R lets hope he doesn't see that monkaS
CaptainAshtar: read the description on the stream if and see what will happen when you ask for the keyboard
DR4GOM1R: oh shit
mltsd: oof just saw it as well haha
inciMage: i wrote its name just google it
scorpiocyborg: got the timeout earlier hahaha
blindhelix: blindhelix subscribed with Twitch Prime.
CaptainAshtar: no notifications...
ProfessorMagikarp0: its prob for the best if he doesnt have text to speech on LUL
Abo7atm: I like how this stream's category is Basic Programming.
CaptainAshtar: yea what are you talking about that's even before you begin?
inciMage: @Abo7atm its basic for some xd
Infinitelym: @Abo7atm i think that's all Twitch offers as a programming category
Abo7atm: @inciMage yeah I guess that's true
ProfessorMagikarp0: i dont think its normal for people at this lvl to stream LUL
gutschilino: is python a good programming language to start with?
yaus_baus: yes
CaptainAshtar: yes
filedescriptor: @gutschilino yep
Abo7atm: @Infinitelym this is the joke
inciMage: no
vay_man: yes
yaus_baus: well depends how you define 'good'
CaptainAshtar: python can do everything
yaus_baus: its easy to pick up
CaptainAshtar: except realtime shits in some cases
vay_man: but start with c
inciMage: start with java
Abo7atm: you might want to get into some C after Python to get a sense of what's going on under the hood
lidermaury: start with metamath
yrreseason: bash or zsh ?
Number___Nine: metamathsh
vay_man: bash
yrreseason: isnt zsh standard in new mac os
yaus_baus: zoomer shell just has better completion
inciMage: @lidermaury Kappa
filedescriptor: start with BASIC PogU
CaptainAshtar: start with low C
mltsd: start with assembly and program a better language
lemonboxed: start with some basic programming
Number___Nine: low brow C
MuscleMario: what is up erry1
Crappy_Wizzard: so what is he doing?
yaus_baus: start with Holy C
yaus_baus: no other answer
inciMage: @filedescriptor i started with it it was nice
Oweiii: ale chłop szcza
CaptainAshtar: toilet C is the best
Number___Nine: HolyMetamath
filedescriptor: @inciMage boomer
vay_man: you can literally hear him pee
Abo7atm: Holy C all the way
yaus_baus: TerryPilled programming is the best
mltsd: i find machine language really helps you pick up on the nuances of computers
Abo7atm: dont need other language after that
CaptainAshtar: he doesn't care he is god mode
vay_man: hands
CaptainAshtar: he already did before coming her
lidermaury: look mom, no hands
inciMage: @filedescriptor im 21
mltsd: tru
Number___Nine: open architecture is gonna change everything
lemonboxed: sounds like Tim Leary
vay_man: true
CaptainAshtar: toilet then eating nails
yaus_baus: hearing 'AI' thrown around at ODSC last week was.....
zoki_macola: WutFace
lemonboxed: AI is already decensoring japanese adult videos
filedescriptor: @inciMage dijkstra wouldn't be proud of you
lemonboxed: trippy
mltsd: oblivion AI is where it's at
TheKoreanZombi: Update my priors George.
Abo7atm: @lemonboxed epitome of AI if you ask me
inciMage: @filedescriptor fuck him and his shortest shit
Number___Nine: open hardware, bro
Crappy_Wizzard: I'm still wating for the japanese to start making ai waifus, but they are all lazy bastards
YouPowerRush: sikk
filedescriptor: @inciMage D:
vay_man: thats deep
ickystickybandit: eloquent word salad
Santiago_LHC: @Crappy_Wizzard Start? They are almost finished
fowlmoves: !project
ravicat: LUL
Abo7atm: used it wrong?
Number___Nine: lmao
inciMage: @Crappy_Wizzard already made. they just dont share
Number___Nine: boomers invented forth
lemonboxed: what does it mean to be a Turing complete space
vay_man: google it
yaus_baus: ctrl t
Crappy_Wizzard: @Santiago_LHC what? they haven't shown a single waifu ai to the public yet, what are you talking about
endeavor_42: George looks like he's about to do instant transmission when he points his finger to his forehead
alycia: i
vay_man: lol4
lemonboxed: if you share a waifu ai, then you would be cheating on the waifu
Santiago_LHC: @Crappy_Wizzard ah, you were being serious...
yaus_baus: look at that extremely useful syntax highlighting lmao
Number___Nine: wAIfu
MuscleMario: @georgehotz I am in vim, I want to add a character at the end of the line, how do I do this? I recently ditched my arrow keys and dunno how to move to end of line w/o a command end-of-line when going to insert mode.
yaus_baus: shift A
Abo7atm: capital a
MuscleMario: shift A my dudes rock
vay_man: end='char'
yaus_baus: i use shift A so much man
MuscleMario: i use spacemacs usually tho, so i hope it works, usually i'd use ctrl-a and i think ctrl-e to go from start to end
MuscleMario: but that doesnt work in spacemacs
yaus_baus: tbh doesnt really matter use whatever you like more
Number___Nine: why would you even use vim on macbook touchbar?
Santiago_LHC: because you can?
MuscleMario: spacemacs eats my ctrl buttons, oh i cant do ctrl-a to increment a number.
Abo7atm: what you use instead?
MuscleMario: hurdur
yaus_baus: emacs has its perks when you have a lot of debugging and linting to do
EdwardApollo: Just got here. What are we programming?
MuscleMario: I just need to re-learn to press 'shift A' instead of going into insert mode.
Keyeh: emacs is good when you want to do everything inside it
MuscleMario: I know i could do ctrl-o and hjkl around for a step
Kyoto_o: @georgehotz watched your interview with lex, was entertained :)
mltsd: leaf tea?
EdwardApollo: Lex Fridmans podcast is hella interesting
yaus_baus: @MuscleMario use W and B for word wise movement
yaus_baus: combine with numbers
yaus_baus: 5W = 5 word ahead
Keyeh: nothing beats the speed of terminal vim and command line applications though
MuscleMario: i only know of nw and dw and cw
MuscleMario: i never use b
xGeoTrk: hello
yaus_baus: B = back a word
MuscleMario: Gotta get in dis bit
MuscleMario: i've seen b's used to jump to a character too?
yaus_baus: 0 = start of line
inciMage: yesterday my friend showed my visual studio code at first i hesitated but it looks nice atm
Abo7atm: ^ = first char of line
inciMage: me*
MuscleMario: but i usually just /regex
Santiago_LHC: VS Code is lovely
Keyeh: personally, i wrote a custom major mode for latex in emacs to write my thesis in, so everything was really smooth
MuscleMario: i think i know how to move around good eonugh in command mode, its just insert mode i am misusing now after years of using arrow keys
yaus_baus: just esc out of insert when not inputting
Abo7atm: vimtutor can give you a good start with vim
yaus_baus: dont navigate in insert
MuscleMario: ^ that
MuscleMario: lol
MuscleMario: yeah, hard to unlearn
MuscleMario: im out here like, left left left left up right left left
andrewVadeika517: yo @georgehotz Glen Rock gang
MuscleMario: :D
lemonboxed: muscle memory
Santiago_LHC: I only started learning Vim a couple of weeks ago. It's awesome but it does require "unlearning" a few things and re-wiring your brain for it
yaus_baus: the worst part is writing code in collab or kaggle and not having vim bindings
MuscleMario: I forgot how to use macros in vim too. I used to do an operation and press something likw $w and a period . and then press some button and it would repeat what i did last few steps.
death_gadget: Anyone else use Tridactyl for Web Browser? VIM in browser basically
Kyoto_o: Just use whatever you are most comfortable with @Santiago_LHC
vay_man: yes
Santiago_LHC: @Kyoto_o Oh for sure, but it's good to get out of your comfort zone to learn new things once in a while
inciMage: @death_gadget never heard of it
egon_22: timeout
Kyoto_o: You can still use IDLE an install additional plugins for every single thing you can imagine @Santiago_LHC
Kyoto_o: and*
ravicat: @Santiago_LHC seen it but how is that better and in what ways than typical UI
JoneKone: then
vay_man: wat time is it there in ca?
archeadis: George, I remember you set up a tiling WM in past, why did you switch back to Mac?
MuscleMario: in my office i have no one to talk to about this kinda stuff and lots of ways to skin a cat so... i like to see what other ppll do to achieve the same result but most people just argue about the editor choice itself. >_<
alinutzzz97: How hard is to be a programer?
ravicat: LUL
yaus_baus: just keep to yourself about text editors
MuscleMario: ^ thgat
Kyoto_o: Try it yourself and see @alinutzzz97
MuscleMario: I never push my religion on ppl
archeadis: is this tmux or is it just split in vim?
yaus_baus: vim works for me so i juse it
inciMage: @MuscleMario whats your religion
yaus_baus: i use i3 in the place of tmux though
Santiago_LHC: @ravicat There is something magical about being able to do a quick edit on a file without having to open a full app. You get in, tweak a line, save, commit, boom. It's beautiful
MuscleMario: @inciMage i dont have a religion I think ?
unikid93: @inciMage @MuscleMario his religion is GAINZ
MuscleMario: LOL
MuscleMario: Dude all i GAINZEd in the past 5 years is weight
inciMage: @MuscleMario u wrote u dont push ur religion on others
MuscleMario: FattyMario
kzonixcomua: hi from Ukraine!)
unikid93: hahah noo :(
lemonboxed: you mean mass
MuscleMario: @inciMage I meant my text editor preferences
Abo7atm: @Santiago_LHC talking about something like sed?
MuscleMario: Cult of Emacs vs Cult of Vim
finessin95: @inciMage It's a saying, he didn't literally mean he doesn't push a religion on others
Santiago_LHC: @Abo7atm just vim
finessin95: He was talking about vim
inciMage: @MuscleMario :D
yaus_baus: i think he means the speed of vim rather than booting a bloated ide
Kyoto_o: 😡😡😡😡😡😡 not working
inciMage: thx couldnt read if he wrote sth up there
Abo7atm: oh, i got linuxed away a bit lol
Kyoto_o: What theme does he use? It's easy on eyes
yaus_baus: vanilla vi
vay_man: why is he doing this?
Kyoto_o: That's a default or?
maskerlive: !project
yaus_baus: yeah default vi that comes on mac
vay_man: ??
st47ik: Augur merch George?
Santiago_LHC: His vim settings are on his github
MuscleMario: anyone know off the top of their head what 'vi' command does in vi/vim? Visual Mode -> i == ?
yesokboss: hows it goin george
yaus_baus: vi = shell command to start vi
MuscleMario: nah like
vay_man: never used vim
MuscleMario: 'vi"' selects text in between the "'s
yaus_baus: oh
fillmyvoid: !watisgoingonhere
yaus_baus: yeah
yaus_baus: v i ( = select text inside parentheses
MuscleMario: visual inside
MuscleMario: inside then
MuscleMario: :\
vay_man: is vim good enough?
yaus_baus: yes
yaus_baus: @fillmyvoid I believe george is writing a verifier for metamath programs
inciMage: its nice
robbsalm: so what are you doing @georgehotz ? just got here
Santiago_LHC: Check the title
fillmyvoid: ok just gonna look up what metamath is lol
yaus_baus: http://us.metamath.org/downloads/metamath.pdf
rupan3: boomers invented python
st47ik: nice PogChamp
Santiago_LHC: https://github.com/geohot/twitchcoq
dorkmo: Party1 Party1
Abo7atm: how long has this stream been going?
yaus_baus: 2+ hrs
inciMage: @rupan3 gen-z liked it
rupan3: !time
aziz_fazlagic: 👉
MuscleMario: I just want to take my shit to the next level, and i feel like forcing mysellf to 'hardmode' hjkl will help me realize what shit im doin wrong when i keep doing traversal in insert mode and going to my mouse to move my cursor to a position that may be 15 lines up rather than , 15k or /<searchText> shift-n
Santiago_LHC: Nearly 3 hours
steinlphd: The assert int the Else case is missing parentheses
thebastl: @georgehotz Will boomers see selfdriving cars in their lifetime?
Abo7atm: man's like a machine
Abo7atm: wish i had some of that
Santiago_LHC: Asking about self-driving cars gets you banned
thebastl: Didn't know. sry
lemonboxed: only doomers will c self driving cars
yaus_baus: no comma talk only, i believe
maskerlive: What is twitchcoq?
Santiago_LHC: https://github.com/geohot/twitchcoq
yaus_baus: writing in coq language on twitch
inciMage: googleit
yaus_baus: george'
yaus_baus: flow state is unbreakable
maskerlive: But why is he doing this?
Kyoto_o: It's a very broad subject
Kyoto_o: Anything where you can gather data and manipulate it @shaz3bsec
inciMage: see you guys thx for kind chatting
TheRealMast3r: Don't say cyber to a computer guy OMG
whichtom: lmao
Kyoto_o: LULW what
yaus_baus: lmfao
grizvok: 360 fucking no scoped
poop_balls420: lmao
doomc: LUL
yaus_baus: 420 mlg
PexanKappa: KEKW
endeavor_42: how long has he been streaming?
ellips0nspice: hi
Santiago_LHC: 3 hours
poop_balls420: !uptime
Kyoto_o: @endeavor_42 !uptime
endeavor_42: !uptime
Santiago_LHC: There is no bot
eaterenrgy: 2hr 56min
Kyoto_o: Jebaited
quickfloor: No bot , No pain
endeavor_42: thanks
quickfloor: Have a better life with Nobot.com
MuscleMario: If your shirt isn't tucked into your pants, then your pants are tucked into your shirt.
bubbleboi01: hello
rupan3: MuscleMario not true
PexanKappa: KEKW
grizvok: @MuscleMario no i have a shirt on but no pants
SupaDeviserr: is that 2 space tab
quickfloor: Do we have cooking or QandA stream today ?
yaus_baus: just maths stream
yaus_baus: no distractions
st47ik: 420% focus
taxad0: beucaMD
yaus_baus: man that metamath vim plugin
quickfloor: @yaus_baus is he working in a server ? cuz he's using screen over tmux
yaus_baus: local
yaus_baus: i think at least
0twinshock0: Hi George, i am developer in Brazil, say hello!
st47ik: HeyGuys
MuscleMario: @0twinshock0 hello
0twinshock0: ty kk
beefydangles: yer a wizard georgie
vay_man: voila
yaus_baus: def not following lol
archeadis: anyone know how do I show all tmux windows in the status bar like geohotz?
whichtom: noice
Kyoto_o: im using you as a background noise ngl
rupan3: what is this for?
st47ik: i was kinda following Kappa
lemonboxed: flipping at the meta lvl
robbsalm: @georgehotz Why do you use vim?
quickfloor: @archeadis he's using screen now .
whichtom: metamath is gross
vay_man: but whY?
halcyon8000: halcyon8000 subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 4 months!
Santiago_LHC: Why everything?
Santiago_LHC: Because
robbsalm: why ice is slippery?
MuscleMario: What's his motivation for this? He was doing TwitchSLAM a while ago but... i dunno y he likes the Coq?
vay_man: must be some comma ai stuff
robbsalm: true != false
yaus_baus: not comma related at all
st47ik: maybe cuz its fun to learn new stuff 4Head
MuscleMario: maybe
vay_man: why would he waste hours if not work related?
yaus_baus: waste?
Mendacii_: @georgehotz define “real”
st47ik: @vay_man dude it's fun so there's no waste
yaus_baus: work is waste
vay_man: whats the point of ths?
MuscleMario: ... sometimes u waste hours b/c the problem is stuck in ur head
MuscleMario: and u gotta itch it out of there
aaronfriedland: what is the logo on your sweatshirt?
whichtom: life isn't all work my dude
vay_man: illuminati?
MuscleMario: ^ yes
purgatoires: software engineering is this man's raison d'etre
robbsalm: life is all work
Santiago_LHC: Why does he computer?
st47ik: i mean the whole point is we'r chasing the dopamine shots even if its in solving/learning stuff
yaus_baus: scopie sunday george vs dont work for the man george
MuscleMario: y do ppl do rubix cubes
MuscleMario: and crosswords
robbsalm: just get dopamine in other forms
MuscleMario: SHITS WORK
st47ik: @robbsalm doesnt work like that
MuscleMario: He's taken the LSD and now he's coding from the astral plane
whichtom: lol
yaus_baus: add all symbols
yaus_baus: lmao
whichtom: this is excessive
vay_man: for someone who claims to be out there to create billion dollar company,,this is waste of time if not work related
yaus_baus: hardcode the syntax
lemonboxed: its called being productive
MuscleMario: He's such a brute ;)
st47ik: bruteforce chars SMOrc
grizvok: @vay_man he's expanding his knowledge base. what a "waste of time"
st47ik: ^ LUL
iskjmss: complaining abotu someone wasting their time while being on twitch KEKW
yaus_baus: this is like the purest form of programming
st47ik: @vay_man im sorry MaN but he's free to do whatever he wants to
MuscleMario: Elon muskrat read a book on rockets n now look @ him TeeHee lol
vay_man: I know I m wasting time
rupan3: MuscleMario who
Santiago_LHC: Then let everyone else be
vay_man: thats his narrative
vay_man: dont believe everything they tell
MuscleMario: I'm just trollin in chat @rupan3
robbsalm: isnt functional programming the best?
rupan3: is he a mathematician now?
st47ik: argh NotLikeThis
MuscleMario: The best programming is definitely caffeine fueled
yaus_baus: say it
rupan3: schizophrenia is catchy
asaalgk: what did i miss
MuscleMario: Best programmer in the world, what is this, a hiphop battle?
yaus_baus: !peebreaks
MuscleMario: I crap he recorded raps b4
Santiago_LHC: If it was, he won it
MuscleMario: O
zoki_macola: pee time
MuscleMario: No hands
MuscleMario: Dudes on that stim
lemonboxed: ever chair looks like it codes
yaus_baus: everytime george goes pee take 2 shots
robbsalm: metamath short for meth
lemonboxed: chair stream
MuscleMario: meth short for metamath
Kyoto_o: Do you know who Fabrice Bellard is? Check him out @georgehotz
Santiago_LHC: George pees more often than I commit.
vay_man: hi from India georgie!!
Kyoto_o: @georgehotz or his projects
robbsalm: dislexia god dammit
MuscleMario: @vay_man hi
st47ik: how much tea u drink in a day man? looks like a lot LUL
taxad0: stick to the paper
Santiago_LHC: I want to bind them
MrBankster: you want to use a queue
lemonboxed: f in ass
MuscleMario: i wish.... i wishy wish... python wasnt so popular. Even tho i use it for data shit
AlexEDM: are all you guys in here programmers?
yaus_baus: python facilitates productivity
yaus_baus: fast to prototype
Santiago_LHC: @AlexEDM nah
MuscleMario: yeah, super good for that
LeadCoder: i did on video on python sql injections today. check out my twitch channel
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz is it good time for DISTRACTIONS?
Magistr_Y0d0: Hi. What's that book ?
grizvok: @AlexEDM i am
Quad___lol: you are my favorite reptilian
yaus_baus: http://us.metamath.org/downloads/metamath.pdf
yaus_baus: book ^
AlexEDM: any of you python guys have experience with automating repetitive actions in browser (specifically Internet Explorer)?
zoki_macola: Elon, george and zucc the best reptilians in their class
zeroeagle1: hello everyone
Santiago_LHC: lol
zeroeagle1: alex use selenium
yaus_baus: @AlexEDM like scraping?
doomc: ^
yaus_baus: beautiful soup
AlexEDM: so here's my deal, zero. I want it to work at my job. I was able to install Anaconda, and use Python, but I don't think Selenium will be allowed? hmm
barbudolol: Why not?
zeroeagle1: it's a pip package
worrasenule: thx for this tutorial, berry nice
yaus_baus: why do u need conda specifically?
MuscleMario: lol
128p_: yo y'all
AlexEDM: @yaus_baus for example, going up to click an icon on a page, then enter a two character password, based on what's shown in a certain field
MuscleMario: Selenium is the most widely used driver
MuscleMario: industry standard
zeroeagle1: selenium is great for that
yaus_baus: yeah just write a python script
ellips0nspice: why Metamath?
ellips0nspice: not PLY?
zeroeagle1: used it with python and .net preferred .net tho
barbudolol: Selenium has everything you'd need for that stuff. Not as fast as something like BeautifulSoup but a LOT easier
Santiago_LHC: It better pass
AlexEDM: yeah, I will try to @yaus_baus - I've only made one VBscript - I'm a noob, lel. But practicing in python
yaus_baus: im noob too
AlexEDM: yeah I heard good things @barbudolol
barbudolol: I'm selenium god
barbudolol: if you need any help hit me up
AlexEDM: can u install that easily on work PC's? not to a server, but to my desktop @barbudolol
beefydangles: why was my speech suppressed
MuscleMario: ^ first ammendement
AlexEDM: okay I will send u a friend request, hehe
yaus_baus: pip install selenium
zeroeagle1: ^
AlexEDM: install inside python?? @yaus_baus
yaus_baus: in terminal
beefydangles: :/
aaronfriedland: probably a dumb question but is the best way to learn Python or a similar language just starting a project you're interested in?
hue88: But have you guys ever build a recursive data driven selenium test-framework with elasticsearch ?
Kyoto_o: depends do you plan on going in depth or not @aaronfriedland
yaus_baus: @aaronfriedland watch some intro utube vids
ellips0nspice: too much errors. 99% of programmer work is not program alogrithm, it's bugfixing
MuscleMario: @hue88 yee
grizvok: @aaronfriedland are you learning programming in general or just learning a new language?
cybergenik: What computer are you using?
zeroeagle1: @aaronfriedland do a service that check if geo is currently streamming on twitch
aaronfriedland: not super in depth I just want to be able to automate some of my job and do data analysis
128p_: What are you guys coding lately?
Kyoto_o: that is in depth @aaronfriedland
MuscleMario: I want to get into webgl/three.js to makae a new website
zeroeagle1: @aaronfriedland or get the book "automate the boring stuff with python"
YouPowerRush: did he do et ?
YouPowerRush: on stirm ?
lolwtfreally: I don't know wtf is going on.. but it feels good FeelsGoodMan
MuscleMario: last time i worked on my site was back when css3 html5 came out
MuscleMario: and i handcoded the animations
yaus_baus: all i code is etl and EDA lol
hue88: @MuscleMario but have you used parent child structure for avoiding redundancy and easier test creation
hue88: that's the real shit
aaronfriedland: nice I'll check that out
Kyoto_o: this guy talking about classes and thinking thats the real shit LULW you idiot @hue88
Santiago_LHC: woah, chill Kyoto
hue88: @Kyoto_o O:::: see my last comment duuh
MuscleMario: @hue88 i dunno anymore, i didnt even put elasticsearch in my shit ever... but i stay away from things like selenium cuz its slow and i use it just for testing.
Kyoto_o: bruh moment in here
MuscleMario: @hue88 but i used it in tthe JVM so, meh.
MuscleMario: squadW
Kyoto_o: oh no squadW
MrBankster: scam :O
hue88: @MuscleMario yea I mean I don't see any great uses other than testing anyway for selenium :D
MuscleMario: LOL
Kizzyiee: @georgehotz Thoughts on prome.ai? ..I just finished a 14month contract and wondered what people on the outside thought
MuscleMario: @Kizzyiee gl gettin his attn
hue88: @MuscleMario have you read about webassembly though ?
yaus_baus: george is in another dimension rn
hue88: that's crazy
aaronfriedland: this book looks perfect thanks @zeroeagle1 my job is basically just entering and cleaning up data in excel spreadsheets that has to be made into reports
MuscleMario: ^ barely, i havent done asm in a along time... just when looking at disassembled code
ellips0nspice: too much errors. george needs more phylons for this task
MrBankster: george its cuz bash
yaus_baus: @aaronfriedland if you can replace your excel stack with python you can automate a lot
krnflake1: @georgehotz what are your macOS apps in the status bar? obs, spectacle, but what are the others?
Santiago_LHC: Ah, spreadsheets. The place where hopes and dreams go to die.
MuscleMario: but sounds really cool , lower level things like webasm, websockets
MuscleMario: i never got into
MuscleMario: but always wanted
MuscleMario: Cuz i stay away from webtech mostly
zeroeagle1: @aaronfriedland go on youtube and type automate the boring stuff excell if I recall correctly theres a 40min talk on just that
aaronfriedland: hell yeah
hue88: hahaha yea webtech is actually fun
halcyon8000: Cowbell?
aaronfriedland: gonna try to learn how to use Tableau too
hue88: depending on your project ofc
aaronfriedland: bosses love fancy graphs and shit
grizvok: tableau is pretty nice
Xflagzzz: hello
yaus_baus: @aaronfriedland yeah tableu proficiency is nice if youre a data analyst
MuscleMario: I've yet to work in a more pure math code. Ive done a lotta things, and closest to math in code I've done is some data science crap that was poppin in 2015
zeroeagle1: @aaronfriedland that reminds me when I setup grafana
hue88: @aaronfriedland ++++ fk bout ur code, show them graphs and theres ur raise lol
purgatoires: ggplot >>>>>>
MuscleMario: And im not talkin bout functional programmin
MuscleMario: I'm just saying the field/industry
babadoctor: Is that your cat in the background?
aaronfriedland: nah I'm just a low to mid level employee for a labor union
aaronfriedland: not a data analyst
yaus_baus: @aaronfriedland dont sell yourself short :)
Santiago_LHC: Graphs impress everyone
MuscleMario: oh, yeah, and some stuff trying to brute force a key for a security challenge.
malg0d: George
MuscleMario: polynomial math tho
malg0d: George of the jungle
babadoctor: I swear I saw a cat behind you WutFace
raulciuntastefan: what hes trying to do right now ?
Santiago_LHC: Check the title
malg0d: Jailbreak the simulation bro
yaus_baus: tendies time
MuscleMario: @aaronfriedland to learn the best way is to force urself to read from start to end someones tutorials or the docs. My opinion. Or watch someone code on youtube.. but reading it by urself i think is best
malg0d: Green tea bro
purgatoires: lunch PogChamp
zoki_macola: wash hands
yaus_baus: !peebreaks
malg0d: Wash hands 30 seconds
aaronfriedland: @MuscleMario I can definitely do that
mltsd: too much tea
MuscleMario: @aaronfriedland its good that a lot of professions are now getting scripting in to automate the mundane tasks
programmer42: I'm hungry too! gotta get some lunch
malg0d: Tea is never too much
mltsd: only when too much pee
aaronfriedland: they aren't really encouraging me to automate anything I just hate doing mundane bullshit for $40k a year
malg0d: Green tea
purgatoires: @MuscleMario i just dont understand how it's taken this long, VBA scripting is simple as shit
MuscleMario: @aaronfriedland the only trick to learning programming is being very stubborn/persistant , some days u can hit ur head against something for 4 days b4 u realize what ur doin wrong or rewrite the whole thing
purgatoires: like why now
yaus_baus: b i g g l o n c h
aaronfriedland: infinite lunch
kanogger: Luchstream PogChamp
dorkmo: sandwich
malg0d: Jailbreaking lunch
MuscleMario: He probably gonna eat cereal
dorkmo: avo toazt
xkcdz: PogChamp PogChamp
yaus_baus: george put on some cooking musics
kanogger: JonCarnage
micos7: Bruh where is the avocado toast?
MuscleMario: George needs TTS for Donos
malg0d: Where is that girl she usually interrupts the stream Kappa
yaus_baus: no grills just maths today
MuscleMario: Kapp
aPosterior: binging with george
vmarkushin: @MuscleMario no. He gonna eat ice
MuscleMario: LOL
malg0d: George ping my router
yaus_baus: george refactoring cooking script
kanogger: milkshake with them crushed up oreos
MuscleMario: guacamole... fancy
malg0d: Gordon Ramsey George Hotz edition
acae: gay walk
MuscleMario: Gordo i missed it last nite
malg0d: Nothing wrong with GAYS
yaus_baus: god* walk
purgatoires: cooking is suboptimal
TheKoreanZombi: Let's maximize cooking screen.
malg0d: George I best come up with my ideas during sleep deprivation any thoughts on that
MuscleMario: @purgatoires ok elon
aaronfriedland: lmao
ellips0nspice: Is anybody use HolyC?
MuscleMario: I've heard some1 say Holy C now a few times?
MuscleMario: Wut iz dat
TheKoreanZombi: Dead language
yaus_baus: terry lang
malg0d: WaT
malg0d: WHAT
micos7: git add ingredients;git merge oven;git commit;
poop_balls420: wheres your GF?
malg0d: GREEN TEA GEORGE
aaronfriedland: untreated schizophrenia basically
halcyon8000: Lmgtfy
yaus_baus: rip terry
zeroeagle1: the main maintainer got hit by a train
mltsd: my kitchen messy too and i gotta clean it
malg0d: inb4 copyright
MuscleMario: Astari lol
yaus_baus: emotional terry music
mltsd: but im busy making logic gates
MuscleMario: Geohot listens to my shit
malg0d: George you are making me depressed
acae: ding!
MuscleMario: i think that guy is dead tho
YouPowerRush: highbruv music
12ka4: hi bro
malg0d: No
purgatoires: i hate driving lol
malg0d: George drive through the Kongo
ProfessorMagikarp0: emo george now
YouPowerRush: brow *
ellips0nspice: i develop also interest stuff for devs too. I streaming dev process, check my stream
kanogger: i cri
yaus_baus: doing 70mph in a residential
malg0d: Stop advertising yourself
aaronfriedland: me too but I do it nude on chaturbate check it out sometime
12ka4: can you share your tmux config
W1lkins: driving through compton
W1lkins: it's on github 12ka4
MuscleMario: If I didnt know what he was doin, it'd say he's writing his own lexical parser
malg0d: LOL
kanogger: someone timeout @ellips0nspice
dorkmo: mindspace: close your eyes, picture youreself driving in the subbies
malg0d: I like this song
markovchain21: where is this hoody from? @georgehotz looks super nice <3
valleyisle: itssliThink
purgatoires: yea i wish i had his hair
Maty_Kapsa: sup George, loving the vibe
markovchain21: @purgatoires same :/
malg0d: George what happened
ellips0nspice: @malg0d why stop? developers don't interesting in new tools?
MuscleMario: oh crap
yaus_baus: dont shill your content here
MuscleMario: Anyone here knew of Robert Himler?
malg0d: I wish I was high
TheKoreanZombi: self.esteem = False
W1lkins: ellips0nspice stop advertising your shit in other people's chat
malg0d: ^
Santiago_LHC: No one cares about your stream. It's late to self-promote so hard
Santiago_LHC: *lame
malg0d: He reminds me of Mark Zuckerberg
slinkyone: You’re such a speed typer wow
W1lkins: MrDestructoid = Mark Zuckerberg (no space) Kappa
malg0d: Lol
Macatw: tvgbBrain
slinkyone: blzAldas
Santiago_LHC: George is like super human compared to Zuck. That dude doesn't even blink.
malg0d: I get my meds tomorrow, so I hope he does a stream tomorrow, I'll be high + drunk
yaus_baus: tomorrow is workday
kanogger: what is george even coding today? :(
malg0d: I was on about @ellips0nspice
Santiago_LHC: why don't people even check the title
yaus_baus: reading is hard
malg0d: Skim then
MuscleMario: @ellips0nspice ur stream is a meme lol
zeroeagle1: tomorrow I have like 4 hours of meetings
yaus_baus: F
malg0d: F
MuscleMario: Its just a buncha vaporwave shit
kanogger: N
slinkyone: Only 4
malg0d: NO
torlkhal: where is the chiken
malg0d: Don't you there
malg0d: Dare
yaus_baus: fuck meetings lol
malg0d: Whatever way we spell it
slinkyone: I have a 6 hour code review
kanogger: TriHard
malg0d: Lmfao
malg0d: Stop that
zeroeagle1: At least one is about switching our infra to kubernetes that will be interresting
malg0d: Dear god
kanogger: take your meds
fillmyvoid: why am I getting an ad for lego technic on this stream lol
malg0d: I would if I had them Kappa
W1lkins: Which CI software?
mltsd: does anyone know of any good indoor rain sound videos/apps?
eduardoadf1: PedoBear
eduardoadf1: pedoBear
grizvok: infrastructure at my job is insane
purgatoires: @fillmyvoid ive gotten several makeup adds on twitch
Macatw: do you take notes on what you're experimenting or studying?
grizvok: developing inside of a k8s cluster with skaffold
zeroeagle1: currently we have appveyor but probaly gonna switch
Santiago_LHC: @mitsd https://www.calm.com
malg0d: What is the name of that song I wanna be sad too
torlkhal: whats happening here?
grizvok: dev env is sooo close to prod
mltsd: @Santiago_LHC thanks
yaus_baus: @malg0d nothing.nowhere is the artist
mltsd: ive been trying to find good indoor rain sounds for a while
OnlyB1ade: when did u start on metamath
grizvok: and i just got involved in our new database architecture and am getting to work with the smartest dude on our team very closely
slinkyone: Indoor rain FailFish
zeroeagle1: @grizvok that's nive hope you will learn alot
mltsd: @slinkyone yeah its like a cloud inside your room raining on your bed and shit
mltsd: pretty innovative
yaus_baus: @grizvok what dbms
TheKoreanZombi: And you just got modded by geohotz. what a year!
my_curiosity: @georgehotz what do you think about Rust?
MuscleMario: Anyone here pivotted off swdev after years of exp?
grizvok: @yaus_baus mysql 8
yaus_baus: @grizvok nice mysql is cool
grizvok: @yaus_baus old architecture was master-master but we are moving away from that
W1lkins: don't we need peano.mm in the source code to run verify in CI georgehotz ? and what CI do you use normally, just travis?
grizvok: susceptible to shit like split brain
ellips0nspice: @MuscleMario i streamed my first twitch stream before Geohot in Programming category at 2014. I'm back and do test stream now
MuscleMario: I've only used Jenkins, Gitlab CI, and Bamboo
MrBankster: i prefer const
zeroeagle1: I use appveyor and travis
mosin_lol: what is metamath ?
yaus_baus: http://us.metamath.org/downloads/metamath.pdf
yaus_baus: ^ book hes referencing
TheKoreanZombi: He's asking geo, not you nerds
Santiago_LHC: Geo has no time for stupid questions
malg0d: Okay Korean guy
MuscleMario: @TheKoreanZombi we are Geo
TheKoreanZombi: lol
moepost: !followage
MuscleMario: -illuminati.wav-
malg0d: We have no time for feds
MuscleMario: Watch me do my strut
MuscleMario: watch me do my catwalk
mltsd: fuck 12
MuscleMario: LOL
malg0d: Watch me do my 0day sneak attack
Xaotic: wtf is a crystal programming language?
zeroeagle1: when you have ruby + perl in your stack
yaus_baus: LOL
oksan309: Why u code in kitchen cmonBruh
malg0d: Why not
TheKoreanZombi: because kitchen is bedroom is office
MuscleMario: all these youtube vids poppin up on ppl making MEELYONZ off bug bounties, like... hmmm ... am i doin it rite?
malg0d: They are just devil worshippers making black magic 0days
malg0d: worshipers*
malg0d: Mere mortals
MuscleMario: I wanna be as excited as Geohot waz when he gave his Comma.ai shill at the end of his qemu stateless debugger talk. "WE GON BE RICH! WhoooOO!"
oksan309: @TheKorean i thought it was a fetish LUL
malg0d: We all did
MuscleMario: LOL
torlkhal: PokBlaziken
MuscleMario: Drops the guac, uses napkin to pick it off ground, proceeds to use same napkin to wipe face.
MuscleMario: Been There, Done that.
MuscleMario: LOL he reads the chat
MuscleMario: HAHAH
MuscleMario: Not pre-recorded
MuscleMario: MuscleMario subscribed at Tier 1.
zHamish: bon appetit
yaus_baus: lmao
MuscleMario: I AM NOW
dorkmo: nice save
zeroeagle1: ahah nice move
MuscleMario: Goteem
MuscleMario: I love uu geo
MuscleMario: been a fan since 2013 <3 <3 desu
YouPowerRush: highbrow om noms
ellips0nspice: I'm geo fan from him first iPhone hack SeemsGood
yaus_baus: tendies
torlkhal: git commit push
girtss3: Thank god this stream is live, just came from work, dont want to go back
TheKoreanZombi: guacamole isn't a meal.
beefydangles: TENDIES
zeroeagle1: *git push -f
yaus_baus: uber eats tendies
firstavegner: me too I follow geo when he unlocked the first iphone
deqroys: what am i looking at lmao
deqroys: this is some advance stuff
firstavegner: chat do you know what is he trying to achieve today ?
thebastl: @georgehotz Does sony still hate you?
yaus_baus: writing a verifier for metamath programs
oksan309: Do u do unit testing?
zeroeagle1: @deqroys basic programming usefull knowledge
yaus_baus: well he wrote the verifier already
deqroys: this is basic ?? @zeroeagle1 im in my second year of c++
yaus_baus: pretty different from practical c++ programming
MrBankster: bro. are you in the zone?
zeroeagle1: that's like 3-4 years python basic
firstavegner: vim pro
MuscleMario: in the zone autozone
blackhawk131: Properly using vim is harder than the programming he is doing lmao
ellips0nspice: helps geo write rap language interpreter
smurfd0: thats half the battle, to think for yourself you are getting closer
beefydangles: Pog
Ziv0: { LUL
whichtom: oh boy more math symbols
yaus_baus: boiling point elevation
pedrosantos867: bro, can you help me with an html project?
quickfloor: chicken tinder ?
firstavegner: chat for real anybody understands what's he doing right now ?
aaronfriedland: yeah Kappa
Quad___lol: math is a language of universe and php is a language of retards
jtparker: GeoHOTT = Geo + Homotopy Type Therory
Quad___lol: wait what, srz
Quad___lol: sry*3
beefydangles: its simple really
yaus_baus: @firstavegner wrote his own verifier for methamath programs now proving
yaus_baus: df = df_2011.dropna(subset=['LATITUDE', 'LONGITUDE'])
printhellosailor: I'll never understand why anyone would watch shit they don't understand
yaus_baus: oops
zeroeagle1: @pedrosantos867 is html your main programming language?
aaronfriedland: I'm not even watching the stream I just have popout chat open
pedrosantos867: @zeroeagle1 i'm kidding
zeroeagle1: xD
oksan309: @print out of curiosity LUL
firstavegner: @printhellosailor you will one day :D
aaronfriedland: can't go over my comcast 1TB limit watching 1080p programming streams 4Head
trinitr0x: what is he trying to do?
ellips0nspice: @printhellosailor I understand, i likes programming language devs, why not? <3
whichtom: @printhellosailor if you look at things you already understand how can you learn anything
zeroeagle1: ^
firstavegner: geo u should use chat nighbot for frequent questions and commands
printhellosailor: this isn't the kind of stream to watch if you want to learn how to program
Santiago_LHC: and to auto-ban people who ask about keyboard
oksan309: Someone should report him to nsa LUL
blackhawk131: @whichtom well said
pedrosantos867: What is he doing?
MuscleMario: He's probably using a HHKB
aaronfriedland: sounds like a Topre Kappa
MuscleMario: I have a crap Ducky One 2
phlox____: monkaS
yaus_baus: no keeb talk
MonkaSupreme: can we get a keyboard emoji?
snapcs1: mAYBE IF i GEt the SAme key Board i can bE pRo hAcker liek u
MuscleMario: I miss my arrow keys :(
MonkaSupreme: ⌨️
jtparker: It is a keyboard that has only greek symbols
theGeekPirate: How am I supposed to learn how to program when I can't use the same keyboard as you NotLikeThis
printhellosailor: not sure how you can find watching something like this enjoyable if you have no idea what is going on... but I can understand pure curiosity I guess
mufeedvh: hey George, can I work with you?
trinitr0x: @snapcs1 ajajajajjajaja
barbudolol: hey George, can I work for you?
ThatKevinLima: MrDestructoid MrDestructoid
MuscleMario: @Galus will submit a PR one day.
yaus_baus: lmao
phlox____: hey George, can i work on you
okkessh: whats up with backspace.ai
MuscleMario: Just so I can say I did
aaronfriedland: hey George can I work you
Santiago_LHC: Where are all those PRs
MuscleMario: Itll be like a typo fix
printhellosailor: I never said I don't like your content, was referring the randoms who were asking what is going on
TheRealMast3r: isn't coq a french programming langage
blackhawk131: hey George can I work?
Quad___lol: you can hire me to manage them :)
pedrosantos867: Which is the easiest way to trigger you?
deqroys: how many programming languages do you know?
yaus_baus: !pasta
ThatKevinLima: LOL
MuscleMario: Dont talk about the cleanliness of his floor
beefydangles: check the vod
kzonixcomua: Hi George can i? =)
snapcs1: if you have a good foundation you can pick up any programming language easily
yaus_baus: !peebreaks
djcows: hi Gorg, how to increase volume in windows xp??
barbudolol: I just want to be managed FeelsBadMan
MuscleMario: I have to google metamath
oksan309: How many keyboards u crashed because of something didn't go well LUL
MuscleMario: Dunno wut it iz
printhellosailor: I've been watching twitchcoq since pt 1, but this is the first stream I managed to catch live
pedrosantos867: Which is the easiest way to trigger you?
Heydrian: hi George tell me what to work on?
maskerlive: @pedrosantos867 tu queres mesmo ser banido tem cuidado
Santiago_LHC: Sigh, these people
yaus_baus: http://us.metamath.org/downloads/metamath.pdf
ThatKevinLima: alo portugaaaaalll
ShadySloth6: can somone sum up how far he is and what he did till now in the other2 parts?
yaus_baus: where is @grizvok when you need him
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz is it a good time for D*I*S*T*R*A*C*T*I*O*N*S?
MuscleMario: I really just wanna know how to stay healthy as a dev
yaus_baus: health is a scam
ThatKevinLima: PROCRASTINATION TIME =D
aaronfriedland: ^
yaus_baus: live fast die young
MuscleMario: >_<
yaus_baus: who wants to live past 40 anyways
jagger_rsw: Kurzweil
aaronfriedland: I don't even want to live past 30
mufeedvh: I wanna work with you and win self-driving cars and stuff... you can check out my site if you want... mufeedvh.com/about
oksan309: @Muscle eat alot of carrots LUL
Quad___lol: math is bullshit....its all trash nonsense thats purpose is to keep our minds busy from the real problems - gender studies, global warming, etc...
firstavegner: thanks to fortnite I can watch you geoHotz
zeroeagle1: @MuscleMario watch "david sinclair google talk" on youtube very interresting
MuscleMario: There was this movie, something about time travel, they made a joke, "U know what they do to engineers when they turn 40?" "They take em out back and shoot em"
AtomicPandaAttack: @Quad___lol you are actually retarded
ellips0nspice: Top Geo projects by my chart: 1) iPhone hack 2) reverse debugger 3) comma.ai
firstavegner: Geo are you interested in the research field ?
bubbleboi01: @AtomicPandaAttack he is being sarcastic idiot
NilsIRL: @zeroeagle1 which talk?
snapcs1: what kinda drugs are you guys on
whichtom: damn chat wtf
MuscleMario: Im on the internet @snapcs1
aaronfriedland: Sertraline and alcohol
MuscleMario: Highly addictive
Santiago_LHC: Calm all your pants down everyone
Quad___lol: @AtomicPandaAttack hahaha why are you here duuuudeeeeee
bubbleboi01: I'm not wearing pants KappaPride
ThatKevinLima: this chat is going nuts
yaus_baus: ~Mark Twain. "Life's journey is not to arrive at the grave safely, in a well preserved body, but rather to skid in sideways, totally worn out, shouting "Holy Shit, what a ride!"
oksan309: @Quaq if it wasn't for math u would probably be now in a cave wiping ur ass with a leaf LUL
AtomicPandaAttack: @bubbleboi01 looks like you are the idiot who didnt understand the sarcasm lol
MuscleMario: shit tier ssri my guy
aaronfriedland: I was on lexapro before but that shit didn't work
aaronfriedland: this shit doesn't work either but at least my dick does
yaus_baus: Prozac gang
MuscleMario: damn, i never took anything outside of nootropics and stims for workout
cybergenik: What is coq?
beefydangles: big mac sauce
MuscleMario: its a type of sauce used on big macs
bubbleboi01: @AtomicPandaAttack Lol
zeroeagle1: the recipe is on github
beefydangles: and or a refreshing beverage
jtparker: Coq is a proof assistant for formal proofs
cybergenik: oh I see
aaronfriedland: why is McDonald's Sprite so spicy
okkessh: I have a great playlist to play while coding on spotify anyone interested?
Santiago_LHC: no
yaus_baus: too much shilling
beefydangles: the corps got us hooked
okkessh: it's okay
mufeedvh: I wanna work with you and win self-driving cars and stuff... you can check out my site if you want... mufeedvh[dot]com/about
okkessh: it was fire
printhellosailor: this stream is making me hungry af
snapcs1: clintHard
volere: EAT FASTER
bubbleboi01: just dont eat
aaronfriedland: reported for self-harm
aaronfriedland: pasta too hot
oksan309: Do u live alone ?
chexmixz: @georgehotz Will you be at kubecon in SD?
volere: coding stream DansGame coocking stream PogChamp SeemsGood
Alpasfly: what are you eating?
volere: cook*
Abo7atm: oh it's bedtime, goodluck George!
yaus_baus: gn
hilololow: geo i love u from morocco
infowolfe: @georgehotz why do you use terminal.app instead of iterm?
TheBigK02: do u still go for 1 milion subs on instagram or did u give up
Quad___lol: just pay for the 1 million subs LOOOOL 4Head
bubbleboi01: just mind controll people to sub
volere: omnomnom
MonkaSupreme: @georgehotz do you have movie recommendations?
volere: nom nom nom
volere: *code code * om nom nom
nic0latesla: what are you eat?
MonkaSupreme: or anyone in here got any movie recommendations?
volere: pulp fiction
Santiago_LHC: @MonkaSupreme what do you like?
oksan309: Pomegranate cmonBruh
beefydangles: just unbind it
MonkaSupreme: @Santiago_LHC drama, thriller
mufeedvh: I wanna work with you and win self-driving cars and stuff... you can check out my site if you want... mufeedvh [dot] com/about
beefydangles: Kappa
snapcs1: stop bro wtf
volere: the answer is
a_caspar: ASMR Kreygasm
volere: 42.
yaus_baus: @mufeedvh just apply at his company if thats your goal lol
Quad___lol: @mufeedvh no he doesnt want and its all basic things you "expect"
Quad___lol: expert*
volere: how big is your apartment?
Santiago_LHC: @MonkaSupreme Us, is a great movie
mufeedvh: ok sorry for that
jtparker: Why did you choose Metamath?
Zeitvertreibe: i atched this now for some time, still dont know whats about, but googled.. but t=t might come from (t+0)=t
nic0latesla: No tea?
printhellosailor: LUL
oksan309: Would u agree if someone copy ur source code LUL
NilsIRL: @oksan309 it's not licensed
deqroys: what are you eating
litenull: u remind me of martin shkreli
aaronfriedland: does he still stream
snapcs1: what socks are u wearing what are u eating whats ur favorite color what type of shoes do u have
litenull: he's in prison
aaronfriedland: really?
guy_ross: yup
snapcs1: BrokeBack BrokeBack BrokeBack BrokeBack
aaronfriedland: I thought he was rich
W1lkins: litenull that's a one way ticket to ban city
MuscleMario: So, he actually made his own food. Inspiration.
ProfessorMagikarp0: sub mode Kappa
MuscleMario: Im over here reheating takeout
MuscleMario: And wonderin why im fat
zeroeagle1: concrete proof that oligarchy works
zeroeagle1: nobody is complainning
MonkaSupreme: @Santiago_LHC I thought the trailer was silly, but if you recommend it, i gonna check it out
yaus_baus: any of yall work with folium and geojsons
MonkaSupreme: I've worked with geojson, had to parse zip code regions
MuscleMario: Discrete Math was one of my favorite subjects in school
zeroeagle1: you robust mario ahah
MonkaSupreme: TBAngel
infowolfe: infowolfe subscribed at Tier 1.
yaus_baus: im trying to make a chloropleth to demonstrate density of markers
guy_ross: obviously.
infowolfe: @georgehotz why do you prefer Terminal.app over iTerm? :P
yaus_baus: can i do this with just a list of lat/long data
yaus_baus: with the geojson to definite districts?
MuscleMario: @infowolfe <- same question i guess
infowolfe: lololol
MuscleMario: But but... i like to print out 'fancy' and 'gnome' in my demos
infowolfe: the weird shit is... I actually met geohot back at decon 18 I think it was
MuscleMario: which puts an image inline
MuscleMario: for the memes
yaus_baus: lmfao
yaus_baus: george went down the terry hole
MonkaSupreme: @yaus_baus yeah, whats your question? ^^
W1lkins: I'm writing this message from templeOS, about to head off to meet God
zeroeagle1: templos don't support networkking because god said so
MonkaSupreme: HolyMetaMath
MonkaSupreme: HMM
MonkaSupreme: heard it here first guys
yaus_baus: @MonkaSupreme im just not sure how to proceed with a dataframe of lat/long data and a geojson to definte districts
yaus_baus: i think i just need to read more
MonkaSupreme: @yaus_baus i think geojson is polygons, so you basically have to find out if point is in polygon right?
yaus_baus: yeah exactly
yaus_baus: im doing map.add_child(data=geojson) but its not even rendering the polygons over the map
MonkaSupreme: sounds like something, somebody must have done before.
MonkaSupreme: @yaus_baus don't know what language and framework u're using
snapcs1: no please dont
snapcs1: LUL
yaus_baus: @MonkaSupreme python3 with folium
theslumpedgodxd: Hello papa
yaus_baus: nvm dont mean to detract from the maths
dinomdanom: Hi George!
MonkaSupreme: @yaus_baus you can check your geojson here, if you are not sure if it's correct http://geojson.io/
neroo2k: what happen in the background? Why is there cardboard on the floor?
yaus_baus: @MonkaSupreme yooo thank you, never worked with geospatial type stuff before
Nevermorewinz: the fuck is he doing? i cant code
theslumpedgodxd: Have no clue but it looks cool
neroo2k: @Nevermorewinz this is basic programming men easy LUL
oanto80: Hello there
zeroeagle1: Kappa100
Keyeh: dude, he's a parsing a language in python to make a proof validator
aaronfriedland: ♦️ 100000
Keyeh: you don' t need to be a 5Head to see
tfue_is_dog_shit: who els thinks jsf sucks
MuscleMario: ...
Keyeh: fixed
whichtom: its just that easy
printhellosailor: the joys of python development LUL
Santiago_LHC: Nicely done
printhellosailor: in hindsight, a strongly typed compiled language would have been a better choice for twitchcoq
MrBankster: when you gonna program in java?
beefydangles: D:
MuscleMario: thats what i said... and then i did it b/c Dallas.
zeroeagle1: do you have any opinions on .net core?
behargaming: sup benjyfThumbL benjyfSmile benjyfThumbR
yaus_baus: <3
MrBankster: i like java streams
shieeeeeeeeet: are we still proving true != false?
printhellosailor: kotlin is ok but java is trash
MrBankster: try some yoga
MuscleMario: academia
Keyeh: is asm a sensible language though
Santiago_LHC: Norman, what did you do
tfue_is_dog_shit: java jsf is the worst trash view engine ever
yaus_baus: next project, write the ide???
mrrobot723: Hey bro. Im new here and i love your streams <3
neroo2k: why don't we just use quantum computer to proof this ? Would be easier.
pascalzzzzz: anyone still doing jsf?
tfue_is_dog_shit: a lot of people actually which is sad
MrBankster: use first principals
printhellosailor: Next Stream: VR-based proof development environment LUL
unluckychickenn: im happy to see you r stream, yt i miss most times dizeeLO
MuscleMario: Geo u goin to any conventions talks?
Keyeh: abbreviations PogChamp
printhellosailor: there has to be better tools than just writing those by hand in plain text
vmarkushin: I've tried mmj2 today, it is really inconvenient
Keyeh: @printhellosailor yes, you know... math
whichtom: dudes crazy
death_gadget: LUL
MuscleMario: wayback him
yaus_baus: rip
Santiago_LHC: NO geocities was the best
beefydangles: wayback
MrBankster: rip geocities
Willcantrell1: 😂😂😂😂
dorkmo: angelfire or bust
printhellosailor: twitchcoq is growing
Willcantrell1: The one and only Hotz
shirafx: what's a coq?
W1lkins: green tea = green tea
wiseai: t = t OMEGALUL
shirafx: ==*
shirafx: :(
Hazor90: twitch cock is growing?
Justanotherantiantiplayer: i always hear twitch cock....
Willcantrell1: 😂😂
death_gadget: Coq is too hard??
Santiago_LHC: Sick documentation
mrrobot723: me too lol
shirafx: i showed u my coq, plz respond
printhellosailor: LUL
Rezii27: 10 out of 10
yaus_baus: lmfao
yaus_baus: feels bad
Willcantrell1: Can I touch ur coq
Justanotherantiantiplayer: so many coq jokes
yaus_baus: better than any of my projects
mltsd: holy shit i just joined and this madlad is still going
Willcantrell1: Why is my coq crooked
shirafx: still using ur ps3 jailbreak to this day @georgehotz
Santiago_LHC: Yay, more stuff
W1lkins: oh no
printhellosailor: how bad can it me
sepulsher: @georgehotz What should i do if i feel subhuman because i cant understand highschool math concepts ??? :(
W1lkins: Userone LUL
zeroeagle1: ahaha that file
vukz: lmao
xxdvxx: wut
Chrimo: You doing this out of pure interest?
whichtom: this is a good start
Chrimo: Seems cool
W1lkins: wtf
printhellosailor: just run it 4Head
W1lkins: it's trying to get /Users/smooth/build/mmj2/mmj2jar/~/ Kappa
Willcantrell1: Jebaited
MuscleMario: lol
printhellosailor: LUL
zeroeagle1: I think you need to create a smooth user
printhellosailor: java needs at least 4TB of ram
MuscleMario: min start reserved mem
MuscleMario: max mem
sepulsher: @georgehotz What should i do if i feel subhuman because i cant understand highschool math concepts ??? :(
zeroeagle1: read the issue
Vjasal: Siri is listening monkaS
MuscleMario: i was essentially held back in my math classes by 1 grade level throughout high school, only thing that sucked about it was jumping and skipping math concepts when going to college. Missing fundamentals had me quuestioning things and not getting an intuitive feel to y things are being done up until calc 2 in college. But not everything is applicable and things that matter nowadays in ML dont even get taught in HS/college regular curriculum
beefydangles: siri wants attention
MuscleMario: u gotta learn to learn by urself basically.
MrBankster: this reminds me of compilers class
MuscleMario: l2read
sepulsher: @MuscleMario thanks bro
Keyeh: BEEP BOOP
vmarkushin: help him
shirafx: your coq is impressive